Alex
What are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and I've been speeding on the freeway
What are you gonna do to me? I'm gonna say sir
Registration I'm gonna pretend it's bad
I'm gonna say step out of the car and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes in the bushes
I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay, oh my god. I'm gonna end up in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you. And then that's it my man
I'm gonna make popcorn and just fall my way
With a story on your tongue
Talking like the judge done ruled before
The trial's even begun
You got sparks but no fire
Got smoke but no flame
Just a trailer full of gossip
With my picture on the frame
You take a half truth to the tavern
Let it soak all night and gin
By the time the sun comes up you swear the devil wrote it in
You paint a little shadow till it covers up the sky
But a light dressed like a sermon is still alive
They same the same old gang
The town square type of stone
Wrapping up a means streak in some self-righteous uniform
But I ain't here to wrestle tumbleweeds or argue with the rain
I know the difference between sunshine and somebody's need for fame
The same dust same old and you can dress it up in glory you can make it sound grand
But guys are paying gospel just because it's loud and playing. No, you ain't breaking me
You're just putting on the show
At the room or rodeo
Yeah, you can keep on riding circles in your own
Satchel
I won't be your clown tonight
At a rumor rodeo
No
Spooky oh my god. It's no. Oh my god. I lost my voice. I've been doing this Christine voice
It really takes a lot
So let's say hi to everyone in the chat.
Lace Perks, Jamie's Cowboys, Chanel.
Things are looking up.
A.O. Devil Eyes.
Hey, there's Bunky.
Everybody, it has been long.
Hope you're doing good.
What's been going on?
Oh, my God.
I mean, I can write a book.
I can write a book that I'll probably get sued to say it's been wild, it's been a wild
ride.
Oh, the latest thing today is, oh, yeah, Tripp and Sip, what are you picking that base for
Tripp?
I like Tripp and Sip actually, hold on.
Tripp and Sip?
You know, don't be too mean
There you go
Jumping sips a good guy
Talks about bang bang doing gang bangs and stuff and
One dick in the mouth one dick in the pussy. It's great. I love it. I love his stories
Talking about oh, well, if it doesn't smell too bad. Just plug your nose and all it's kind of wacky shit
There's the link here you open the link to
I
Love it. I love it. Well, can you can you direct me to a
Good street. Have you do you know a good stream? I can like, you know watch that you know, she's not she's deleted
So it's not a problem, but
I'd like to watch some of that stuff
Well, I
you know
The codex is the codex is well in the way. I
Mean the codex is well on the way. I mean, it's already it's here. It's I mean, it's
Just
Amazing you're watching the shit you go play. I know you'd be it would literally I can't even watch a trip
I have to like I just take them
I can actually, and they're all bitches at me,
but I can't watch hundreds of hours of footage
talking about me in a negative way.
I have to put it through an AI transcript generator,
then have analysis done on it,
and then I can read a whole timestamped analysis of stuff.
So, but it's been lately. I think a lot of
Anger, let me see the latest ones. So what's it? What's hers?
Is it just called Christine's 666 it's on on your channel. Let me grab something
You can see what these
witches are are doing to me
Everyone check out panel verse voD's is it's it's help you to the money same it's trip it's trip and sips
Project and he is nice enough to
He has it's everything is there everything is there. Oh
My gosh
All the ones I delete. I mean, I don't believe this is oh my god
I mean, I'm promoting all openly all everything is there
I just have to be careful with the you know, everything is private right now. Well, yeah on my on my channel and so
You know, I except for my original my original stuff
This was fun, I was with April Fool's Day
I had a fun on April Fool's Day if anyone saw his first April Fool's Day episode
It was really good if I could call it April Fool's Day, but I think it's this one because I see myself in a
You know half naked on it. Let me see. This is my own episode
See
I don't know. I don't see that one episode. Hmm. It was called
This trip to they not all go on because I I had one called April Fools or something like that
I don't see that one
That was a good one though. Maybe it's on the next page. Oh, here's Christine Christine's
Christine's morning devotion. Oh my god. Do I want to go to church like Christine's today?
You just run any of our episodes. It's like basically about me. I want to find the Tommy James interview. Oh my god
Oh my god, that's control this show. Okay. That was Christine. Oh, Alexander NYPD. You got 10 minutes. Oh, I like this one
Bronzeberg Christine and Alexander NYPD. I'm sure this is deleted already. So
Let's play this one. Hey Rudy
The botcott cotton. I'm trying to download a private video. Oh
Couple of my oh shit. Oh
Shit, well, those are lost in the ether, you know, that was that was a great episode. I was like, you know half naked
Maybe it's better that it's not on. I don't know. Maybe it was a little embarrassing. I was having make it
I was I was in outfits and speedo and I'm sorry. Yeah, I
fortunately
Looks like a home. Let me see
couple memories thing
Gosh darn it
lots of the ether
No, maybe they're not meant to be seen. Let's see what happened when Alexander ten minutes ago up here
Get up there. This is talk. It's basically talking about me. So I call fair use on this one. I
Called fair use
Alex
We need what are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and
I've been speeding on the freeway. What are you gonna do to me? I'm gonna say sir
Nice registration. I'm gonna pretend it's bad. I'm gonna say step out of the car
And I'm gonna throw you in the bushes in the bushes. I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay, my god. I'm gonna in the in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you. And then that's it my man
I'm gonna make popcorn and just fall my way
No, yeah, yeah, I now I just use these as like, you know when people say the N word too much I say
These are gonna come on if you keep saying the n-word and they usually will shut up 90% of the time unless
They say a Sandman wants to see them again. He does but you know some people will say no, no, no
No, I'm sorry. I'll stop. I'll stop and they stop saying it. It's awesome. Here we go. This is it. Oh, here we go
Here is her number one secret regular milk or oh regular milk, but she does it dead
There's fozzy bear
Okay, hold me fast forward a little bit
Chatting with Christ you have okay Christine 666
Here's the thing. I'm currently seems to be
You
It looks like the whole time the whole time she's been talking about me and your NYPD. Oh here we go
Okay, Alexander NYPD show your fingers typing
So good morning everybody. I hope everybody is having a beautiful April 2nd. I can be here long
I don't know what happened last night.
I do go to sleep at night.
I know some people don't
and they wanna keep the drama going.
Hey, Moni.
Oh, they wanna keep it.
I don't know what you'd like.
I'm not gonna be too long though.
Mr. Alexander NYPD apparently seems to think
he has a few things to say.
And I'd love to hear what he has to say.
Let's hear Alexander. So is he on my side waiting for I don't know
Watching we've been conversing back and forth on my community page. Let's see
Here's the thing
I'm gonna stand my ground
especially with a very
drunk
delusional
Oh mama kept I will hold my panel very well with him. Trust me
And if you have anything to say to him, you're welcome to come up because he needs to be told that he's here and there because I'm getting us tired of him.
Alex, we've been together many, many years.
But many, many hours.
And nobody's ever said you had to choose.
I did. No, it's not a mistake, momma cat.
I, here's my, here's my, I ask that you don't hide people.
You can time them out.
She died on a chicken.
They start crap.
We've got to have a little banter.
We're going to have that for adults.
Some people don't know how to act like adults.
So I want to make sure.
that the people, because I don't like it when I do go into other chats, and they say horrible things about me or my family, and some channel owners seem to think that it's okay for should be free speech, and I get it.
I allow free speech to a point, but now when you start attacking women, children, elderly, or family.
Excuse me? Excuse me? Excuse me?
So there's that. That's why I've given wrenches out. Oh my God. Don't hide. That's the only thing. You know, you can play with them and give them a five minute time out.
Why was it immediately banned without even realizing? I'm not going to sit here and take it. I am a nice person. I always have been a nice person.
And then you've got these illusional, drunk, drug-addicted idiots.
I think they're being ganged up on by two, three, four, five, six, seven, ten.
How are there many people?
The situation is they are not gaining up on you out of malice.
They are not gaining up on you as a group.
You, sir, and anybody else.
Do things into to individuals. What do I do? Maybe the same thing you're doing to the 10 different people
That is why they're calling you out
Okay, let's hear I want to hear all that Alexander hit that link
You want at this live?
I'm doing it for you
Because you need to get yourself straight
You don't have to like me Alexander
Hey, Miguel. How are you? You don't like anybody?
But you're not going to play both sides of the facts.
They come up here wherever I met.
Oh, much a good lady.
And then that old ad cut.
No, Alexander, it doesn't work that way.
You can be friends with a lot of people
without putting somebody else down.
I think that if I'm talking about somebody,
somebody should say, what have you seen?
Blah blah blah blah blah. Well, and I'll never make anybody choose
But I will watch those that come into channels where I'm at and say hi or try to be nice
or any of those things and then you turn around we post a
disgusting picture
One of my dogs putting me out there
Putting anybody you put it yourself on my show your whole face. Not in high school. We're grown ass woman. Sure. I'm an old head. I don't care. Call me that all you want. Start. Right. I mean, we continue making pictures of me.
Good morning, Lulu. How are you, sweetheart? I'm just going to go further. I was just walking home to McDonald's. So.
I'm going to mute up for a minute.
You all chat and let's see who's going to show their rear
their ugly heads.
So one moment.
Your god was that
The fuck was that
So up so why would you do I mean there's motherfucking shit
Okay, so what you know, why'd you want to talk to me so much?
I really didn't. I was actually just listening to the song I dedicated to summer last night.
I didn't even know you were live. And then I saw it.
You told me to go live.
I did, but I didn't think you were going to.
All you say is I'm never like Alex up, so why would I think you would go live?
Well, it's only for a few minutes.
Yeah, you'll find out, Bron.
So, well, you know, I don't understand why you won't talk to me anymore.
So what's the deal with psychoronies? I don't even know honestly, but one has because you don't know if you heard the beginning
But here's the situation Alex
You know, I like the enter wait a minute. Let me let me talk. I like banter
I'm okay going, you know back and forth call me an old hag con that doesn't bother me
But but I've not made one picture of him not one not one video
That is me
Are his family's name? I don't even I know he lives in Redondo Beach. That's all I know his lies
Can get somebody hurt
including him
He's going to go look at his panel right now, and it's all gone
I don't want you at all. Okay. Well, so there is no more videos. There's no more sure
Lies as you people call it. Okay, you know why
Yeah, because you can't try something that's not there and he's getting strike every fucking day
Well, so I told him to do it
More moves like he erase everything and now you can't get strike and that's fine
But let me tell you something if he's private them or unlisted them
People are okay. Why are you help me?
Okay, go go go people are taking clips and timestamps
And YouTube can still find the video and message code we're looking for.
Fuzzy outside.
Yes, and I am going to hold on a second.
Fuzzy is your old Christine.
Just stop messing around with saccharone
Well, but here's the problem Alex, you know, he's no the problem is you guys are more obsessed than him
No, you started a panel the other day at six in the morning
Beater came up crazy came up
Dumbarton love art. They came up Tommy James came up right all talking shit about him. I go to bed. I wake up 30 hours
As a doctor, I tell you, stop praying for God to take away your type 2 diabetes.
He has already sent the cure.
Later, you're still talking shit about the guy.
Alex, let me explain something.
I've never gone live at 6 a.m.
I've never had a live.
You know what live I'm talking about?
It was like a day or two ago.
And you all going in on him because and you know come on you know why people aren't gaining up on him and then Amanda
Choms in and then ten hours later any panel you're on
Saky-saky-saky dirty finger now you got a campaign dirty finger operation or something Amanda
At bronze, please be very cautious with words. Okay. Oh, of course. Yeah, bronze a bit of chicken
Bronze chicken, they called you an eagle tonight. Hello. Get this welcome shit out of my face, please
Well, you can't trust you sir. There is what do you mean? You can't trust me?
That's bullshit you can't trust you said
Are you out of your fucking mind?
All right, so let me say this to you Alex.
I don't know get this welcome shit off our mouth.
Let me just say this one thing.
Nope. I'm not backstage worthy motherfucker.
Thank you.
Okay, but Alex you have told everybody you're going to porn about me.
Exactly.
So why would I?
Who did it?
I would never
You've done it before
Oh my God, to left and fucking money, not to Christine and someone
It doesn't matter who
Remember Harry, you did it to Harry
I did do it to Harry, 100%
Those are things that deserve it
I would never do that to you
You did it to me
How many nights have we talked about killing your husband with cyanide, Christine?
You think I would throw that all the way over a cock?
Alex, I don't know how to talk about that.
You have.
Exactly.
Those were precious moments for me.
Alex, I mean.
You on the band?
The fuck?
Hey, all right.
What?
The whole situation with your boy, right?
The problem that we have with him
is that now he's on this.
He was on this for our guests because he deleted everything.
He's on this rampage.
About find all of our information one little cat guy
Against 30 people attack. I don't know what else you want to tell you
You gotta just listen, bro
So the thing about it is he's out here the whole picture thing that should a stupid, right? Yeah, that's retarded
That's not it. Actually, but the thing all of this comes from all of this the bottom
Is there do you understand all of this comes from?
No, I don't need he made an enemy of himself
How we're gonna have everybody
Because the thing about it is the way since he had since he got monetized. He started acting different and we're acting different
He started treating everybody like shit. Then he sat there and Docs
Be the first
And put it up there
I said, did you hear what I said?
He docks Vita.
Then after that, he docks allegedly docks
Ally Masters computer.
Then after all that shit.
Good, that motherfucking deserves it.
Then again, if he's the one standing come into his house, he deserves that shit
He wanted to be in a troll community, so that's what happens
You guys turn the minute it shit you
100%
He did it to himself
He can't handle it. You guys took advantage of it
Isn't it a little parody
of having a nice guy
and because we're all competitive
now, this is what he did to them
in the community he can't handle
Well, who the hell are you the community police the guy just on YouTube with his own parents?
He keeps coming back complaining about how people send stuff to his house
You know, you know, who's this one now? So I'm just I'm really not a thing of what you say
You already accused me of calling the cops on him yesterday, and I'm like, I ain't calling. I know I told them about it
I keep lying on you
Yeah, he keeps lying on me, right? I ain't calling no cops for him. So the thing about it is Alex
That's your boy. If he doesn't want to deal with trolls and don't come to a troll community or just shut the fuck up and take it
The answer just pop it on YouTube. He actually tried to bring us together
Fuck listen to this guy's house. Like what the fuck is that?
Alex has bullshit
It's not bullshit. That's absolute bullshit. Oh, he has ever done is try to destroy all the people
I just don't want
Psycho rollings with a little piggy pillow
This come on
Yeah, this is what I'm saying
Don't say he's trying to destroy without proof. So prove. Oh, I got a lot
Show me words when he tried to destroy and I'm gonna come there with a millions
But together and gave love
We would love to you try to give out, please tongue
I'm interested. I don't know the guys
Speedos his balls fell out. Is that not a damn about him show himself. That's disgusting and I don't like seeing that
Okay, so the thing about it is that in the day your boys right? He doesn't have good intentions
He says something and uses people
Manipulates
You know, this is my own opinion. This is my own opinion
There's some hefrews didn't do anything. Yeah, the heifers you think because the heifers are laying low for a week or two
I know it hurts to hear it. I know it hurts for you to hear it. Psyche is not a good person
Yes, he is
I'm sorry for you to hear it
I don't give a fuck what you say
I have my own opinion of the man
What bronze first test is not gonna change that
You think he's cool
I think he's cool
That's not gonna change brother
You can like psyche
And you can still want to oh, thanks mom. I don't need none of your permissions to like that guy
You guys think he has dirty nails and he's a loser good for you. I think he's fucking awesome
And that's a problem
It's called free will
Okay better now
Yeah, but what the fuck this guy's telling me who to like and I like like what did not say that I did not say
Please hang with us, but then don't go to him and talk shit about us. I don't
You will switch it up, bro. You do that. You will switch it up. No, no, I do not I mean I'm a switch in baseball
No, I can back away and hit home run, but I
Hope you was joking about yesterday on Steven's panel in chat talking about Bronzeberg is next don't don't do that again
Okay, yeah
Well the way you keep it up and you might be these guys aren't fucking and have you heard these motherfuckers who who you talking about
I don't know what my mom's for cooking neck. He possibly could be the way
Who are you even talking about?
You know who we're talking about the trio being my piece rolling up between the six and eight train on for the man
You're not gonna
You're not gonna do that. It's not happening Alex. It's not happening Alex stop it needs to stop
Your trio can do as they choose just really alone
You really think the trio is going to do something to me? Alex, please stop it.
You can't even why what are you? Why do you special? Why can't the trio smack you up? I don't get that
It's the goddess because you're big talk
No, it's not that that's what or anyway
And and psyche we're here for Christine of beta Tracy everybody talking about psyche 18 hours straight and you are jumping on it
No, that's not even you don't even understand the foreground story you don't
Alex you gotta realize
He says he's high blood sugar. It's not a sugar problem. It's a sticky blood problem cutting carbs fixes it
Being ganged up on but he doesn't realize and he needs to realize that he is going after
Everybody so if he's going after everybody. No, you see it as going after I see it as protecting himself
You're going after everybody's going after him.
What the hell is the guy supposed to do?
And what was the list?
He's going to put you out and disappear and die
or go back after them and stand up for himself.
And that's what he's doing.
Just leave me alone, Alex. You don't understand.
What was the list for then?
He left you alone.
What was the list for Alex alone? Alex even oh my god, you guys are so funny with the
Christmas season. I wasn't even talking to that man. I'm on the list. I'm on the list.
So yeah, I am good. It doesn't bother me. The list is just dumb, but I'm just trying to understand
what was the purpose. This is a mentally ill man making a no, I disagree with that. I think he's
And you want to take that but I think that's going to be a downfall
Thinking that it's his downfall. What do you think he's exactly what he's doing he's something like insane person with dirty nails
He's baiting all of you. I don't care. He's baiting me. He's easily he's on stream talking about he wants to unalive himself
That's his fault
No, he doesn't he? Oh, so you don't remember what he said?
Okay, so if I said that right now, you're going to take hysteria and make temporal, so Alexander?
How many times have you said that?
I am mentally ill. I'm insane, Christine. What are you talking about? According to...
According to my life cycle variation. I'm out of my fucking mind. We're all crazy. I even admitted. I'm crazy. Yes
And then they had to tell me they'd be like Bronzeberg chill out and I said, that's how I show y'all I'm crazy
You know what you look like bronze but to me when when I saw the picture for the first time you like Gary Coleman
What you talking about like he money is not black. You know that right? Yes, he is
You want me to pull the picture when he is not black?
All right, he might not be black but he's have Afghanistan or something
I called that dirty beard fucking three and it's definitely not the picture that Harry thinks it is with the mustache in the hair
That's not him. I
Called him last night after getting maze. You can't tell me what I screen-shotted you don't what he was long
I've been fucked up Alex Jesus fuck you now you're trying to gas like me
Like, oh, it's a lie, like, we're in a delusion of dementia.
Bitch, I have it on my phone right now.
I got, like, 30 screenshots of it.
I was looking at it before, like, I can't believe that's him.
But whatever, I'm not here to attack money. I just want that lose little money. I'll be in a criminal
He doesn't pay for mass transit. He just thought I don't know
That's not a cool citizen. That's definitely
Buddy, I'm ever gonna hang out with I'll tell you that
That's not like a friend of mine on YouTube. Yeah, we cool. I love money
But I would never associate it with someone like money in real life
Well, I don't associate with me in real life.
A hundred percent I would then you protect me.
And why do you say shit about me so sad, so bad?
Seriously, Christine, what do you talk about?
Because that's all I do up here is protect you and
Even last night you you told psych or sometime through the middle of the night when I was sleeping you told I didn't
Make this morning
Okay, well this morning whenever but you told me you'd never be on my panel and you're at
Yeah, because I you've been saying it. I will never let Harry
Alex or those three of us
There's another third, right?
I will never let them up ever, ever.
You say to be there in summer.
Oh, well, those three I would never let up.
And you laugh about it.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
I don't want her forever.
Like that's so fucked up, man.
The fuck?
Let me tell you something, Alex.
I was the third one though it was three hours as many hours that you and I have spent in backstage
and talking and talking together and watching movies I found your heart that's the only reason
I tolerate you because I know that we have bonded deep inside
You know, I'm recording this because I don't want to hear shit later on like I
Love you, okay, if you say that you would associate with me in real life like the summer when I come to New York
Why would you even talk about your pals coming after anyone in my group?
What a horrible person I am
I didn't tell him that.
Wait, Christine, even better.
Christine, even better.
Remember the time he said,
I can't wait until Christine,
and someone comes up here.
I'm gonna be on the first.
I'm gonna meet them at JFK and blah, blah, blah.
Like, he was doing it in a predatory way.
That that I was fucking around. Yeah, like easy will be a new work. I'll be a JFK
We're gonna be at different airports waiting for you guys
It's going away Alex that little piece of heart and found fondness I found of you. Yeah, it's a hard way
Yeah, it's a harder. Why? Why is it going on when?
Because how you treat me and other people, you, you, you.
I haven't talked to you in days, baby. I know.
This is the first time I've been up on your panel.
Yesterday, I dropped down on Stephen King's panel because.
Well, Stephen King's a pussy. He lost my respect last night.
But because of you, I dropped down. I haven't wanted to share a space with you.
Making our bed. What am I supposed to do? I gotta keep moving on and live my life. I'm sorry
Whatever you gotta drop off cuz I'm there because Alex
Because you make it unbearable
Christine right we were there before for us. Yes, we were
Exactly so and now you like I can't share a space with them
You do that that back and forth you you switch hit her man you play defense and to be honest
I don't want that dude psyche anywhere around with a fuck communities on I'm in
I'm just saying for myself
I don't give a damn what his sexual orientation is
He's he does not he's not a good person
How is he not a good person?
If those that's absolute. Yo, if he's not a good person under the devil the guy
Little cat crying about you guys all day. How is that? I don't get it. You understand what manipulation is
Gaslight yeah relation, you know what that means, right? That's what he does
And not to you though, you're not even there if anything. He's got
Every night I bought him a dog tonight again
There's been so many times I've mind about business every day
Bronzeberg this bronze where that you couldn't wait to see what the fuck I look like
I don't even give a damn about that. But the thing about it is by the way
Black asshole out there. So you
Bronzeberg this bronze where that you couldn't wait to see what the fuck I look like I don't
even give a damn about that but the thing about it is by the way every black guy ever so you blend
into society my god honestly you have like no defining features like my eyebrows don't be like
yeah that's him but you just look like every other black asshole out there so you're good
I don't care about I don't care about the looks let's get to the point he is not a nice person
Easy. Hold on. Why do you have a scar on your face though? Is that from a cox smacking you? You have like a scar. Stop talking about my looks. Stop talking about my looks too.
What is that? But you have chicken legs. That's what I don't get. You feed in the face, doesn't match the chicken legs that I stole. Let's focus on the subject matter here.
In the raw leather. There's no way you're...
92% of people who have tingling or numbness in hands or feet are missing the warning signs of decaying nerves.
Brother
You're muted brother you're muted brother
I heard you on I heard you on beat is this morning. Yes, you're like, would you see it?
Hi, it's me and they're like it was like the one was like that's Arthur Bita and she's like
There's no way that was Arthur.
Yeah, they just fall for this shit so easily.
I don't know what's wrong. I mean, it's like, I knew it was you.
Before you even got the first word, I was like, oh, someone's backstage with...
I don't want you to say backstage psyche or something.
Hey, it's me.
Oh, it's me.
It's me, guys.
Oh, hi, Sweet Pea.
Guys, it was so funny because on Christine's show, she's like,
oh, here's Sweet Pea in the chat.
Hey, Sweet Pea, I was making sure it's with the banner up
and everything.
Sweet Pea, is that you?
Yeah, it's me.
Oh, okay. Here, guys, meet me.
No one knew.
We're like...
And he's like, and Arthur, I analyzed that transcript.
I said, is there anything nice in this show?
Anything defensive of me?
Oh, the no-no buttonhole, please.
And Chris...
And the transcript said,
yeah, somebody came out and said,
don't shit on Psyche.
Oh, wow. Look at that.
That was you. Thank you.
I always got your bag, brother. Trust me.
Oh, oh shit, Q
Hey, yo, fuck you, Arthur. Hey, yo, fuck me nigga. Oh
Wait pause. All right, show pause pause. It's only wrong. Yeah, pause not not not cat paws either
Hey, we've been our guests, let's welcome. We're having a full panel right here. Oh shit another one
No, it's not quite correct.
Who the hell is Lesley?
Lesley? Who the hell is that?
I thought it was more like Lester.
That's little tickly toes.
That's Lester the molester.
No, I never thought it was one of those.
Tickly toes?
Uh-oh, I hear Geddonis going on in the background.
It's always in the background and it sounds like there's like...
Some crack or being I'm waiting for the smoke alarm chirp the African ceiling bird
Okay, I need your modding skills in the chat right now. You get up you go away. She looks different. Oh
She kicked you kicked you bow. Oh shit. You can be rude. I didn't hear
Okay, good. Good. Okay. Well, maybe that okay. I thought I thought he was being here
What did I even do? I needed you? I don't know
I'm not even a mod. I'm not even a mod
I didn't even do shit. You just be you just be happy to kick me off for no fucking reason
He's mad he's so mad don't be so mad
Only an hour away psyche I'll come there and put you over my
I said I'll put you over my knee. I didn't say anything crazy
Yeah, I'll put you over my knee and yeah, I'll put you over my knee.
I've never heard of the.
I love that.
Yeah.
You never heard anybody say that before.
You're going to.
I'm beat us.
And I was like, oh, I bit my knee to where I was like, yeah, you bent over.
She's muting me and her cat and then she says I'm like the only person
Allowed not to like stream streamer, you know, I mean fucking
Tripkick makes her like the wicked witch of the west and like, you know the girl from the craft and you know the black widow
And I just want to like, you know, just like watch like watch five minutes of her show
Welcome to hell.
Did you lose your voice?
I know.
I lost it.
Yo, Q, yo, Q, what up, nigga?
What's up, Ember?
Spoke here.
I don't know if it's cool.
I don't know.
Nah, I ain't saying that.
It wasn't bad.
I'll say what up there.
It's good.
I miss you.
I see nothing has changed around here, Psyche.
OK.
Yo, how you been doing?
How you been doing, Blondie?
Good.
I think you're really good.
You look like a real estate agent, is that true?
Yeah, it's back.
No.
I mean, if you look like, I have like...
I mean you could wear a pants suit in the day no
my god I don't have a dick look no dick
Don't have a dick. We've been called that before
She got a husband. She got a husband
Nice
We never he never proposed
How long you guys been together? No, not that long two years. Okay. Okay
No, it's not like I'm only like seven years and we're not no I'm not the one doing it everybody's always
Yeah, two years
No, and I've been married before I don't need it
Looks like a Raiders cheerleader and it's like this is your girlfriend and you're not gonna like save up two months of your salary
to find this fucking beautiful woman, a nice diamond,
and fucking, let her start planning a wedding.
I don't understand.
I just don't get it.
Yeah, I'm on here trying to turn you straight.
Hey, I'm straight now.
Well, actually, because now there's a clip of me.
Tommy James, I think have you ever have you ever tried have you ever fucked a woman before?
I went in one time I pulled it went in went out and then I just put my hand
in her vagina and it didn't feel good. It didn't feel good.
I was staring at I was staring at the guy in the porno the whole time while I did oh my god
it didn't feel good like you didn't like the vagina did not feel good around your cock like what the
she was like kind of like she kind of had a big vagina and so it kind of like what oh my god that's
not that's that's that's a fake thing that's not even a real thing bruh no there's timber tightness
that's to have vaginas definitely it was like a dick in an arby sandwich no there is there is
cute um i i do pops yeah well i'm not i'm not here sticking my dick in one vagina and then into
another one 10 seconds later to like
taste the difference like that's a mountain goose flavor like we we when we order speculums to do
pap smears they come in pediatrics small medium large and then like extra large so there's also
what's your size what's your size i'll never tell no in the commas sutra in the commas sutra they
describe them as like there's like the horse of vagina there's like the uh the cow vagina and
Yeah, there we go, like, you know, that's like members like in the 70s women like that was before like they invented the razor or something.
No, I don't remember.
I'm not even talking about that.
I was talking about the roast beef.
I remember having Arby's again.
You can fix that with surgery though.
Yeah, you can get your roast beef trimmed off.
You can have surgery and get a whole dick implanted.
I mean, I'm sure you can do that.
It doesn't really work that well.
Anything.
Honestly.
It doesn't really, like, I mean, they can enlarge the labia
together a little bit and make a little shape out of it.
But it doesn't work the same, I bet.
I mean, obviously, yeah, it's not a real dick.
It's like...
How about penis enlargement? Have you ever done a penis enlargement?
I've never even I've never seen like a patient with one because I do primary care
So I don't actually do that stuff
But I've seen people come in with like implants when you know when they've had like prostate cancer
And everything gets yanked out and they can't get they don't have any muscles to get a burner anymore
They have like a rock they can have a rod put in which is always hard or they can do this thing that is like a
pump
And the pump goes like in there growing
and you just like press it and then like it goes,
do, do, do, do, do, do, and can't get hard.
But I've never, I never fucked with that either,
but it works on me.
If you do the rod or you do the pump cue,
what would you pick if you had to choose?
Yeah, would you just always be hard?
I would choose the rod and I would just like, you know.
No, fuck being always hard that would suck. No, but you don't you don't feel it though
It's just like but you're always yeah, you have to live your whole life with your dick in your waistband and that's crazy
Yeah, there was a guy
I saw that at the there was a nudist resort. I used to hang out at the other coast of Florida and
They called him footlong Fred because he had one of those in
planet all the time. So he not only didn't have a long gonger,
it was always hard.
But that's fucking weird. Especially like imagine you're
going to like a family restaurant. Like what do you
want to do? You want to be fucking you want to be pitching
a tent in a restaurant?
Having 12 inches of hardness all the time. Like what the fuck
do you do with that?
I see these movies are these black guys.
Fucking 0.01% of
hell no.
Have you ever seen these black guys and some pornos?
It looks like there's an arm.
I was like, what tribe from Africa are they?
There's like so big.
I was like, is that real?
And seriously, have you ever heard of that or is that real?
Yeah, I've seen some crazy shit.
There was a guy, like I was like 19.
And at that time I was just a nursing assistant
in the hospital and he overdosed on cocaine.
And I guess one of the side effects of that
is that you can get like a perma boner
that doesn't go down and you have to come in
and then have it drained so that it gets blood flow
and doesn't die.
But this guy had it drained and still wouldn't come down.
And it was like, it was the biggest dick I'd ever seen in my life.
No, I did not suck him off.
Oh my God, no.
Not a fucking porno.
No, but I was like scared.
I remember like at that age, I'd only seen like one or two
penises in my whole life.
And then like I go in there and I'm like.
What are we supposed to do put ice on it like if they wanted me to pack in ice there are some porno's
I've watched where the guy goes in and he's like oh, I just I don't know. I can't I have an erection
I was sick that day
But this is that's what you find out for a woman.
That's not what I find out.
A real big charisma.
Your eyes got real big.
I love that.
This is the eye approaches.
What the fuck.
What are you, are you like a nurse or something?
I'm a nurse practitioner.
A clientele.
Hey, and I've been told like, you know, cause
That's why your house is really nice.
I've been told like, stop harassing nurses.
It's all right.
I mean, I can just tell it's, it's all, it's updated and modern.
I sell home improvement.
So I know exactly, your shit's very updated.
Yeah.
Okay guys, someone diagnosed me by my eyes.
Oh, you definitely got pink eye, got a little light on it.
I think we're good.
Too many rim jobs.
I haven't had or given one in years.
I know it's so sad.
It's really sad.
Sounds personal.
Arthur, can you help me out with this?
You could fucking do heroin into your neck.
Here do you want to see how you know I have money?
I'm gonna show off once I don't ever show off anything, but I'm
The car it's the car. I don't know
My god my new fucking car
No
Bum-bum-bum
Look at my heart of clothes in here
It's a Tesla Model X plaid
Oh, you have a plaid? Oh shit. I hear it's so fucking fast. I had so much fun
That's literally I don't know people if you don't know that's literally like the fastest car you can buy
Like the quickest car you can buy the Tesla plaid is fucking insane
Yeah zero to sixty in one point nine seconds. That thing is nuts dude. That thing is fucking that that's faster than like a fucking Bugatti
Hey, yeah, Tesla made of Tesla Elon Musk just decided to like put all the balls to the wall in one car
And that's what she has
Hey, well, you know, I like
I just like rock, you know, if you've heard of rock, but I don't like rock anymore
I used to be able to do all my animations on there and now it doesn't work for me
But that thing is so funny though because you could pull up on pretty much anybody
They could have like a car that they put $50,000 into and you'll just smoke
That thing is so fast, it'll break your fucking neck, like...
Yeah, it's fucking fast, it's cool.
Look at this shit, look at this shit.
It's it's so I'm gonna show you something
Okay, so this is so fucking cool you walk up to the car right notice
I'm not touching the door handle or anything already it might be mad at me because I closed it
But it fucking the door opens for you like when when your phone comes in here
Yeah, it's really cool
There you go. There you go. I love it. I love it. Do you like driving? Do you like driving with the yoke?
Um, the yoke I do not like and here's why I'm super tall
So
When I'm driving with the yoke and or when I'm doing the auto drive
I'll show you if it turns. Oh, it's locked right now, but it turns
It'll hit my my knees and then it'll drop me out of um auto drive
Wow, look at that Navi system.
That's a nice Navi system.
I think you can, I'm pretty sure,
I'm pretty sure if you, like you can go to Tesla
and get a regular wheel on that thing, right?
I feel like I heard something like that.
Yeah, you can, it's $800.
It's not a big deal.
Guys, guys, you know what? I got a good time cat toy.
It's cool, but is it so pretty?
There's a Bucky's padded sofa in here that I got my son for Easter.
Those things are just so hilarious because they don't look that much different
than any other regular Tesla, and a lot of people just don't know about them.
So like when you fucking, when you turn into a rocket ship, nobody even realizes it.
I mean, it's a total fucking mom mobile.
Look, I have a fucking stroller in the back in the back of it.
And I look like they just look like regular ass Tesla's.
But if you don't know what that little plaid badges on the back.
Yeah, that thing's going to dust your ass.
It'll get you know, but it'll get you and the falcon wing doors.
She is like a real woman.
It's so nice.
Yo.
Congratulations.
I'm just like, you know what?
Like people say Hellcats are fast.
That thing would put a fucking Hellcat to shame to put that in perspective.
Like that thing would, that thing would annihilate a Hellcat.
Justin and I were racing on the highway and he tapped out at like 170 and was like, I'm
done.
I'm not, I don't want to play this game anymore.
170 kilometers?
We're going to.
170 miles per hour.
We're crazy.
What the fuck?
Yeah
Yeah, I'm telling you Arthur that's literally like the fastest production car like on the in the planet
Like there's it literally doesn't really get that much faster out of a factory than that car. No, I gotta go on YouTube
I got like this. I did a Tesla plaid is is nuts
I mean the only thing that's really gonna beat that the only thing that's really gonna beat that is if some dude has a
Fucking Lambo with the twin turbo and fucking drops like 50 grand into it and
Mods all out. That would be like the only thing that's touching a Tesla
Plaid car. She's a cool car. Okay.
But I think I have the coolest grocery bag.
Hey, look at this one. What?
You have a different grocery bag.
Is that what it is? It's supposed to be a grocery bag or is it supposed to be something else?
Because it's a carry anything cleaning supplies. You know, you know, I guess you can throw
If you have a kid you can throw the baby in there. You can carry the cats in that
Yeah, that can be a cat bag. Yeah, this is a Victoria's secret grocery bag or yeah
One of them will try to jump out but then the other one like if I put her in a bag and carried her around
She would just stay in there. She wouldn't give a fuck. Hey, okay, so Jamie's like my choice. I've the choice
I may make me wonder why
I have controversial people on the show pretend like I'm pretend like I'm not Barbara Walters
pretend I have like a little bit of Elmer Fudd boys and I'm a five foot tall British woman
that wants to be a newscaster and this is a fucking weirdo bro I know but you know
Paige and Benny last night hit it off you know I've actually met Benny in real life like I've
I've been there I know what the situation is I know the scale of it well I mean
Yeah, I've actually met him twice, but I only went I went to his house one time to hang out with him
That was like really before I knew about the whole thing, right?
And then a couple months after that is whenever he fought his mom and that whole thing happens
So then you know, then I basically told him if I ever see him again
I'm gonna snack the dog shit out of him and then since then it's kind of just
Okay, so Benny like you know, I mean he like says a lot of shit and stuff and he did like open hands like no
He doesn't just say a lot of shit. He does like crazy shit
Maybe he's crazy, but you know what my son put hands on me. He'd be dead. Oh, that's it. It'd be a wrap
17 did my mom if anything my mom beat my ass when I was like fucking 18 19 years old like I could you know
Obviously I was in a position. I probably could have
Looked her ass if I wanted to but no, I mean, it's your mom like
And it's like but she came on the show the other night
I've never seen her when I was on his show. I just like would see oh my god
Yeah, because she has a hundred pounds on her. Okay, so fucking flirty diamond probably has a hundred pounds on me
Doesn't mean I wouldn't beat boxer brains in like what do you mean?
That's a fair fight because you're both guy. Okay. Yeah, you're both admit it fine
He hitting his mom was inappropriate
it's inappropriate but if you look at him and his mom like some people have this
relationship with their mom or this like what bro don't
no some people no no no no no no it's like come on don't do i'm gonna stop you right there
yeah i've never seen her in the back you have you ever seen rosanne it's like darlene versus
Oh, come on, psyche.
They're the same sex.
I don't know about all that.
You're gay.
White trash fights with each other.
I'm sorry.
They do.
Well, psyche, I'm just going to just let me just let me say this.
I understand that you like Benny, right?
And I understand like people, like when you like somebody, you'll kind of,
you'll look past shit that they do, but it's not worth it.
Correct.
like you're just going to make everybody look at you crazy to defend somebody who comes around like once in a while.
8 a.m. is now we're going to get paid crazy? No, everyone would know. Well, that's normal.
No, listen. You're not listening to what I'm saying, though.
All I'm saying is that you're going to make yourself look crazy and say that over somebody who only listen, listen, listen.
I'm not done. I'm not done. He only comes around once in a while.
He only comes around once in a while. So why make yourself look crazy over that person?
Yeah, I'm sure he's gonna be him. He'll be a mainstay on your panel, right?
He might be because you know, like you're doing great, you know, and I want to know help me start my channel you help me
So if I just like to get him to his first 50 subscribers again start live streaming
He told me about the requirements for live streaming. I know it's like I'm just like bro
He's not worth the trouble that having him on here and being his buddy
He neither is like so many people that I have on I don't care
I mean, it's like, you know, whatever like roast them like, you know, tell stuff about other criminal record
Let them reveal themselves to be assholes and bad people like let them reveal themselves
Why can't why do they have to just be like shoved in the corner and
the shadows, I would never have mentioned their name.
I don't understand that part.
It's their show.
They're not gonna reach out to your screen
and hurt anybody here, okay?
What the fuck?
Why do you sound like a girl when you say that, Arthur?
I'm copying Sweepy when she says it like that.
Sweepy, what the fuck?
Arthur, can I talk to Sweepy, please?
Hello psyche. Hi, sweet pea. What happened? I heard you quit YouTube because it's because I made you upset or
Or you had elfin tight as I heard
But it's like how about like just you just separately you don't have to be on when he's on and stuff or you can like be on
And like to talk to him, but why does it have to be if it's a Barbara Walters interviews Charles, man
Not like I'm saying Barbara Walters, but say
Like a journalist with it like about as popular as me. Let's say there, but she's just starting her career
She's an interviews Charles Manson. She wants to ask him. Why are you so crazy? What like what happened?
What's going on in your head? And it's interesting. This is I love true crime guys. I love true crime. They don't
Yeah, they got the murderers a profile of is that like a bad show because
I don't know I have a different perspective if you don't agree with me, you know, I stand alone really
Thank you. Are you a good dancer? Let's get some dance moves. Oh, no, please. I saw him twerk
Oh, what do you want me to do?
He's a freaky dancing.
I mean, my dogs are real.
Stop.
We have to fill the way.
All right, all right.
Jesus Christ, I'm sorry.
I feel like it's like a puppet.
Someone had you like a puppeteer.
Oh my God.
You're a very spectacle, buddy.
It's monkey, Jamie DM'd you.
But she said she doesn't have discord anymore.
She got, oh, she got, um.
OK.
She's not got discord.
So she, if you, she can get your other.
Yeah, I got a laptop discord.
And Samman DM'd you too, it sounds like,
do you want to talk to Samman?
Just ignore his emails.
Oh my God, Samman doesn't want to talk to me.
Well, he wants to talk to me
because he's on my show every episode.
And then he said, oh, thank you.
And he's here every time.
And we heard you said last night,
it's gonna cost $20 to let him back on.
Yeah, yeah.
And I'm gonna say by the, this time,
do you want us to sponsor Samman on the show again?
$20 that's gonna be I mean he makes $20 and fucking $5 off of everybody that gets kicked all the time
He made like $200 that way off of me. That's why he always is like
Well, I don't know why you dorks keep going on his panel fucking let him sit there and just recap control
I'm gonna assume for residuals and I'm gonna win in court because he plays all my content
Everybody's like either playing big trolla doing her lip liner or me crashing out. That's his show basically or him playing
Terrible terrible. He's literally a dumb person
And I'm not just saying that to troll him and because I don't like him. He's just a dumb human being like he's not a smart
He agrees everyone literally everyone agrees
He's a fucking idiot like he doesn't even understand what he's arguing about half the time
Like he just talks to talk and sits there and makes fucking noises and does like onomatopoeia
That's what we should call him fucking onomatopoeia Andy
Yeah, I'm gonna call him autumn on PS Sandy. That's all he does is go
Yes, I do same and send me some money fucking retired
But don't put the carrot in front of me. So I say yes, I need food and then you don't send me money
Do you ask talking about but wait wait wait wait? He keeps talking about me doing a door-to-door job
I guarantee you selling shit door-to-door. I make more money than you. I guarantee you
Sam and it's called it's called a job. I even have a job. I get hourly in commission off of this shit that I sell
And we're talking about hundred thousand dollar projects
Like shut the fuck up. I haven't gotten a hundred thousand dollar project yet. I've had it like 10 bucks. I got
Hi, I've had some pretty fat ones, but not a hundred thousand dollars
So shut your mouth as much as we are willing to send me. I'll eat it today. I need to gain about 150 cubs
You need to like, yeah, you know, yeah, oh my god, relax chill
That's scary I can see your heart beating
That's what everyone says
I can see it beating right past the BKG tattoo
I'm gonna get a cue told me put fuck over this one and then I told you to put a donation goal up to put the word
Not one person, but you know what the other side I'm gonna get you have to okay
But that's the point of a donation goal. You got to keep it up there. You got to be consistent with it
You can't do it one night and think that they're gonna say it, you know, put it up
Instant gratification
Well, you'll pay for my tattoo.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's only going to be like a $50 tattoo.
It's only four letters.
It's not going to be expensive.
I will go today.
I will go do it today and I'll put FUCK over it because she just teases me about it all
the time and throws it in my face and I had like actual love, loyalty and stuff to her.
So I'm going to put FUCK over it.
And the BKG, that's a Lenore's angry at her now because she was so mean to me.
And I will go today, if you have a, I don't know.
Go get the quote or the price, thank you.
Let's see how much it is.
Okay, I'm gonna call on the, I'm gonna call on the.
Do you have my number?
Okay, can you put it backstage?
Okay, I'll put it backstage.
And you can text me and let me know how much it is
or FaceTime me there and call me or whatever.
Thank you so much.
Let me go see.
I'll go today, and then we'll-
I want you to be happy.
Hey, it's Bunky.
By the way, you are on my channel
and under my recommended channels.
I think you're on the first tier of it,
like, I don't know if you've been streaming or anything,
but, you know, I like, I love you, you're awesome.
Yeah.
I have not been streaming.
I have been completely off the internet.
Guys, wow guys, this is what you know, this is what like this is like fucking what the friendship is about
You know, it's like this is what friendship is called. I'm a little bit
Well, I know what it's like to have a tattoo on your body that hurts your feelings and like
I feel like every day I can't stand looking forward like looking at it and stuff
Okay, so yeah, really what we will the the goal is here
We're gonna get you have to go to the same shop and make sure you get the same font obviously
I think it imitated I'm gonna find the closest one because I walked that day to find the tattoo parlor
I literally walked about five miles there and five miles home to get it
I'm just saying if you're gonna do this it will be worth it to make sure that that's you know, it looks normal
Okay, I'm gonna call it tattoo parlor on the air shoe right now. I'm gonna find the look we're gonna get the letters fuck on top of the kitty
Yeah, I give him an estimate of how many inches long fuck needs to be in how long how many inches long is your probably like four
Here's a tattoo it's like okay see that I had I said put it in a kind of Arabic letter saying three four inches
Yeah, I don't think you don't have to match the letter and you can just get fucking whatever font you want to do
It would look crazy though. If he got fucking like and like the
It looked like a fucking stamp that he like did it over it
That's if you want a stamp look if he wants like stevo style tattoos, that's up to him
I don't know if that's what he wants to do though
I mean, at least get it in a, and I think it has to be in the same font because then it'll look normal
It because if it'll look too wild and weird
Then he's just gonna regret it for a different reason
It will document the progression you get it with the stars burped you get it like a stamp
over the side of it like like, you know, be this kitty gang is like
canceled
Yeah, well RG the only thing I would say is I think the the cat of part of the tattoo
It should have been more like detailed and cool. It's just like kind of a clip art picture of a cat
That's all
You it was if I especially since you're a white boy you should get some color and drawn hand design like based on like a lot
So if we looked at I mean, it's it's like I have a black cat name Lenore
It's also kind of the anarchy cat a little bit. I don't think it's like terrible, you know, it looks like it looks like a
Like a Chinese basketball team's logo. It's okay. I like Chinese people
Looking for my phone. Okay. Did I fall off first? I can't I'm back
You're back. You're right. You're all good
Maybe I'm not
I see you I see you am I here? Okay. Yeah, you're here. You see me, but I don't see you
Anybody here's funky
You can hear me come on stream yard, I left my phone number in the back chat
I found it.
Hello, Sparky.
I hear her.
Hold on.
I know.
I'm just fucking with her.
Okay.
She's fucking with me.
I'm going to take a picture of the tattoo and then I'm going to call the tattoo.
I'm going to tell them.
I can text them.
I'm going to do a local place.
I can Uber over there.
I'm going to get the quote and then we'll go do it today and this will be fun.
I've already had a drink.
I'll drink another one before I get there.
Like I did the first time.
I was so drunk.
Be careful.
Okay, well, not only that but like they might not even tattoo you if they sense that you're like super drunk
I'm very good at like pretending. I'm not drunk. I'm very good
Regular is retired and it will blow it out. I know
Well, we know that but
They're gonna want a guardian signature
Sure, I haven't gotten a tattoo in like six or seven years been a long time
I don't even remember what the tattoo gun feels like.
Okay.
Is anybody else here with me?
What, woman?
Why'd you put your phone number in the back chat dickhead?
So fuck.
Can anybody even hear me?
Now Q gonna dox you yeah
You're lucky, I don't know where you live Sam and I would just I would send you hella concrete
Make your fat ass fucking carry it downstairs. You wouldn't even know what to do with it
I'd send you so much concrete you wouldn't you really wouldn't even know what to do with it
You're so fucking lucky. I don't have your address just to be honest with you
There'd be concrete hookers fucking
Sissies walking up to your house fucking everybody you could think of scrappers
Fucking oh my god
You're fucking lucky
One day it'll happen though one day, you know everybody gets docs
You'll get doxed eventually and then I can have some fun with you. I
Know your entire life is based on you know
Internet fucking dorky discord drama. I'll give you something to cry about boy. I'll give you something real to cry about
Dordo Dordo Dordo
I don't understand why my job is like,
or you don't even have a job.
You sit on fucking Discord all day.
If you're not in Discord, you're in an Instagram chat.
If you're not there, then you're in a YouTube chat.
If you're not there, you're on the panel.
It's all you fucking do.
You don't get no fucking pussy.
You ain't got no life.
You ain't got no fucking friends.
You live for the fucking internet. You live off of people paying you
To clap other people off of your fucking dorky little panel. That's literally your lifeline. I
Know why you work a fucking eight hour a day job and got enough time to be on here this much
I'm just saying unless you're a security guard, which at that point
How are you making fun of anybody's job? Anybody can be a fucking security guard and sit their fat ass there
This is called cooking.
You don't know how to cook, you just talk about it.
Can you even speak in full sentences or do you just speak in phrases?
Little fucking weirdo, little fat ass.
Ugh.
God, your gene pool is disgusting everybody in your family's ugliest sin
That's how I feel about your gene pool boy
I thought people, like, that were like Puerto Rican were supposed to, you know,
I thought people had good genes down there, you know.
I didn't think they were the ugliest people on Earth.
Then we come across Sam and
then we see what his mother looked like and his sister looked like and it's fucking awful.
It's honestly hard to even, it's hard to even put it in words how fucking ugly they are.
I don't know what you're talking about.
And the time, I think they said four o'clock, which is like an hour from now, so
All right, she said depending on the font and the size is what would determine the price
You'd have to know like exactly what fonts you're using
How big you wanted the tattoo over top of that? I wanted this exactly like it pretty much the same same as it as the other lettering
And I need a quote because somebody's gonna be paying for it
And I need the quote for that if you know you wanted the letters as big as those letters. Yeah. Yeah
He's a very skinny man
They're Arabic letters
Okay, oh my god Jesus Christ
I'll promote your tattoo parlor and stuff because I'm a live streamer, is it okay if
I get a little discount to promote you?
150 would be the lowest you could do.
That's a low absolute, but she's the best, but I know I'm asking is she the best?
She's the only person I have available, so.
Okay, I'm gonna leave. I'm not going to you then. Goodbye
You just lost a fucking client for that.
Bro, listen, $150 for four letters of just black ink is crazy.
There's 150 for my whole other tattoo.
It should be 100 max.
Yeah, I'm going to have a renegotiate.
And it's like, he won't even say, is she the best?
I'm like, you know, if you work, someone works for you.
You say, yes, they're the best.
You don't say, they're all I have available right now.
What a fucking douche.
I mean, seriously, what's wrong with you?
What the fuck is wrong?
RG, $150 for four letters of only blacking before the tip,
because you know you're going to have to tip them at the end.
So, I mean, before like, dude, it's going to end up being a $200 for four letters.
Come on.
It'll take fucking 10 minutes.
RG, I walked.
RG, I walked into the other place.
They said like $250 or something.
I got it down to $150 just because, you know, I'm kind of pathetic.
I say, is she the best?
He won't even say she's the best.
Goodbye, nigga.
I mean, Jesus is crying, man.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, I'm gonna tell the blue rings. Thank you so much. See, that's actually the RG instead of saying, oh
Look at this blue rings, which is what we are they say you gotta tell them
Yeah, the blue ring is right and you promote them and stuff. Oh, we're really busy right now
Well, cuz you only have one fucking bitch working for you. They won't even say it's the best you stupid idiots. Sorry
The best around nothing's gonna ever bring me down
Man, where's that fucking where's that Josephina pack I don't got no more blunts, okay?
Yeah
Yes, we got just smoke a little bowl ran out of blunts
You're wasted right now. I'm gonna be even more wasted when I get there, but they're gonna give me the tattoo mark my fucking words
We're back
I'm marking your words right now, psyche
No, they're gonna
Even psyche said last night that he was puffing on that Josephina
And I was like goddamn right goddamn fucking right you are boy
That's the only shit we smoke around here I
Don't even ask they don't even have to ask me what strain I want when I go to the dispensary. I'm like
You're like, oh, yeah, he he's gonna want that just for him. I'm like you goddamn, right?
Okay, things are looking up. I I told him if he's too fucked up
Blank you once again, I'm calling once again. They might refuse to tattoo him
Hi, I heard that you're the best most reasonable tattoo place in town. I'm looking to get a tattoo as soon as possible
I need four letters
Put over another tattoo. It's on my chest. It's not not too terribly big. I've been getting quotes for about a hundred dollars
I'm also a live streamer. I'm at 30 currently. I'm 39 people in my chat watching and I'll have more more watching when I get there
I would just need a quote because someone's gonna be paying this for this for me to get this and
I can be their ASAP
Um, but I just want to make sure all that's okay, and if not, you know, I can call other places, but um
It's um four let four letters if you can you can give me a
I'm a a number to text you the picture if you need if you have anyone available today if it's okay
Absolutely absolutely. Thank you, sir
It's looking good. It's looking good you guys
Well, I am on live stream rg what you you nigger
What's that laughing face for?
R.G.
Yeah, and I'm a chatterer, I'm R.G. I'm a chatterer.
I'm a...
You're...
R.G.
You're about to lose your wrench.
No, I'm not an entertainer, R.G.
I'm just fucking...
In my opinion, one of the best.
Oh, well, you can go watch Logan Paul, though.
He makes only a billion dollars a year, no one cares.
I'm making McDonald's, you know, once a month and Jesus.
She's talking about my father again, Glocky.
Are you serious?
She talks about my family today too.
That's really sad.
Christine's talking about my family.
She's talking about, oh, you just had fun,
kiddie just got paid.
This woman is just sick.
She also talked to big people with my family's picture.
Hello, sir, how are you?
Okay, okay, and that's that for her
Christine's also like 65 years old so she really doesn't have anything better to fucking do than this
Yeah
Guess that's why I dip out for like three months at a time
Are you drinking alcohol or what
absolutely is it absolute no it's a peach to rock and sprite zero so we're
supporting diddy gotcha I know it's not a good thing to do but
It's it's funny though. I'm just kidding because a lot of people think that did he owned any sort of like steak in
Sirach and he never did he just promoted it. He got paid to promote. Yeah, did he never own Sirach
Sirach is owned by like a mega fucking corporation that owns a bunch of other different fucking liquor brands
I love you Spongebob
Also, sir, rock is really fucking good. So I don't I don't hate on anybody
What flavor of sir, rock is it each peach sir, rock and sprite is the best god
Funky stop it stop what you're doing right now stop this shit. Oh god stop cheating on Justin with online freaks
Cut the bulls you're right. You're not cheating with me
You could you could try to cheat with Q, but you we all know that Justin's gonna come in there and fucking wreck the place
What do you mean you mean what
I'm on here talking to them. I think he cares. I think you fucking cares. I think you don't want to see the signs
All right, you want to see the signs that this guy fucking loves you fucking you're shitting on him every fucking day
You're coming on here whoring around with fucking people
Newsflash you're not 25 anymore spunky you're not fucking 25. Let's cut this shit. I
Think she's wearing a fucking wig
What was that have to do with it? She's cheating on Justin. I don't care what you're talking about fucking n-word. I'm talking about her wig
Dude don't worry about her fucking way. We're about your fucking way
You're not talking to the homeless guy in the tent with the fucking spray. This is a fucking real motherfucker who's gonna fuck you up
You're a big talker when you're running away
God help me please forgive me God forgive me God for what I've done I didn't mean to sin I'm such a sinner
Motherfucker please fuck out of here with that
Hey what are you even talking about?
I'm not VB bitch what do you mean what the fuck I'm talking about what are you forget the last
fucking three months of your life? I don't know what you're talking about God forgive me
what are you talking about?
Yeah you ran off like a bitch after you sprayed the poor man in the face with the fucking mace
Oh what did you want me to do stand there and punch him?
You ran off like a bitch and you started crying about God. I walked away God. You didn't walk away. You ran off
You ran off because there's a hit on you in the fucking homeless community now, that's why you're in high
Oh, there's a hit on me in the
There's a hit on your fucking ass. Come on. You know your monkey ass did wrong go back down apologize to the guy
Go go beg him for your journey. You can't make this. You can't where do you where do we find these fucking people?
From the community that I created cut this shit man, everybody's seen that shit dude, come on
You can't take that back. What happened to VB. Did you forgive me B for what she did to you?
VB, you know smokes a lot of meth, so
Yeah, she's always kind of like off in her own little thing. She just gave you a place to stay for fucking six months
And that's all you know, that's just shit on her. Why don't you?
It wasn't even her house. It wasn't because you wouldn't fuck it tell the truth
Was that the reason why it wasn't even her house? She wanted to fuck you and you said no
No, that never happened
That's slander lie husband the husband wasn't down with it, right?
God that's slander and libel. That's true. It's all fucking true
Maybe I know you're listening get your fat ass up here
machinations
Let's put this shit to bed
Don't want to bring this up again
hold the pepperoni, send him a mushroom pizza, maybe he'll fucking calm down a little bit.
Spunky, come back. It's too early for this. You can still fix this between you and Justin, trust me.
She gets a little sensitive sometimes, you know, you gotta forgive her.
And what was like you go he was on fucking hold with customer service
No women want to be around you. I know I understand I understand
Yeah, just like that faggot black dude that you were fucking hitting up after you ran away. Remember that one
Well, cuz I came across him. He was fucking kissing you up and down. You can't what do you mean came across him?
Q don't try to rewrite history. Everybody saw this shit
You can't hide the fact that you're a fag, all right, bro
Just fucking except so because I talked to gay people on the fact. Oh, no, you don't just talk you were like fucking
You were fucking six days
You were curled up with this dude for six days in a tent don't give me that shit
What the fuck is going on?
Baby, how you been how you been you look good? What's with the hair? Is it a wig?
He says it's the way I guess the way all my hair has been shaved off
You're stressed out.
Is Justin stressing you out?
You going bald like him?
Did you guys break up?
Yes or no?
That's all I want to know.
No.
I had a pretty serious moment, though.
Yeah, you want to see it?
It's not really bald.
I'll show you guys.
You ready?
I mean, I'm not like super into it.
Do it!
Are you ready?
Oh, yeah.
Look at that.
You did it.
Look, look, look, look, look.
Ah!
God for you, it looks better that way.
I told you it was a wig.
Leave it like that, it's better.
Yeah, everybody knew it was a fucking wig.
I mean, no one's that retarded on here, right?
Well, I mean, some people have bad vision, you know?
They couldn't see.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Leave it like that.
No, I like that.
Yeah, don't get me wrong.
You look like a cracker.
No, you look like a fucked up version,
like a Gwen Stefani or what's Avril Lavigne
or whatever the fuck.
Miley Cyrus is what I need to know.
Do the devil horns.
Give us the little devil horn action.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there you go.
Take that screenshot of somebody.
Yeah, you're gonna screenshot that
and like do something when then I'm sure.
We'll post that.
Yeah, that does look better.
Anyway.
You could use your regular hair, he looks better.
Thanks, thanks, thanks.
But like, I don't know, I wear my,
I wear wigs, I'm a weirdo.
Is he taking you out tonight or not are you guys going with that that's
That's not a very good wig you can get a better wig than that
He told me to talk to you about something. I don't want to bring it up, but uh, oh god, Goddy. Is it true?
Hey, is it true that you kicked him out of the house?
No, no, you kicked him out of your house because your son had the black dude over again
I didn't kick them out of the house.
He left it at home, and we're cognizant.
Well, that's not what I heard, but OK.
Oh, my god, Kate.
Kate, if you fucking, if you went bald, Kate,
you would look like the fucking, you'd
look like a baby doll.
You know that Justin's a homophobe.
You know that.
And you know you're not supposed to bring certain things
around the guy because he gets triggered very easily.
He's not a homophobe. He's he's just racist. Just respect that respect that he's a homophobe
He's not a homophobe. He's not a racist. He's not a fucking racist. Trust me. He's not a racist
He's a fucking racist. He works with black people. He's not racist. He's just a homophobe
Okay, you can work with black people. It doesn't mean that you know what you know what if a guy's a homophobe and his girlfriend isn't
You know that she can change his you change him just by saying give me no no we have plenty of like gay
Friends that he is super cool with he's not a homo, but he is a homo for he's not a racist
He's a homo. No, he's racist. I've known the guy for seven years. He's not a homo. I mean, he's not a racist
Good, are you racist and yes, that's why yes, I'm both I'm both a racist and a homophobe
Spunky I'm gonna put something in the back chat real quick for you. Okay, okay
There's a private. Yeah
To a few solicitors for like 10 bucks
Oh, he just put his fucking results back there his last test results. Oh, shit. Oh, please
Fuck dude, really? Oh my god. What the fuck you've been doing, man
So he hasn't had sex in like over a year two years two years now two I've had sex in over two years and
You know, I don't really want to the last guy I've been on grinder tried to trap out my house and I just sent him home
That's because you're hanging out with black people
He's waiting for that dude. Yeah, I mean, yeah, I should have done better. He's waiting for Chris K
Yeah, I saw a clip of Chris K getting his ass looked by some like five six fucking black dude the other day
I love you. It's really, it's really laggy, but he definitely got fucking he
I think those Mongos boyfriend
He's okay
Listen, this is spunky loves me. All right
I can say whatever I want
She's cool with it
I know
I will still spank you
Don't start your shit, fuck it
You know what happened last time you started that
fuck it shit
You fucking kicked me off your panel dude
Don't let it happen again
You're gonna slice my throat
Oh my god
Get out of here
Justin, you're in this chat, but you didn't come up here.
He's a little bit unhinged, but you know what?
I still love him.
I was like, oh my God, I was looking for this Willy Wonka
clip the other day.
It's like, Beatus and Oompa Loompa,
and J-Dog are Oompa Loompas.
I'm Willy Wonka.
I found it.
I think I found it.
I was looking for this yesterday.
I couldn't find it.
Have you ever seen the Willy Wonka clip, Spunky?
I don't think I have.
Pick this out.
You will love this.
And Kee, are you still here?
Yeah, I'm here. I'm sorry.
Okay, check this out.
Look at this.
It says, the Anamita's Kidney and Psyche Awakens.
And here is the clip.
Here we go.
One second.
If your time to you is worth saving
Well then you'd better start swimming
Or you'll sink like the stone for the tide
They are changed.
Station we had was about you and like you are seen on LD 15 and I said you keep doing exactly what I fucking tell you not to do
over and over
I left your channel because of that.
I'm not crying you guys, I'm not.
I'm just lost my voice.
I'm not trying to be mean, I'm just patient.
Michael, you're the one that needs to cry, okay?
We're watching.
All right, go ahead. Don't be fucking like that. What is it's about?
That's another thing is like your
All right, Michael, just shut up.
Nobody even gives a fuck about your M-Quicks, OK?
Michael, look, we see.
With all the respect, the only person that really cares.
I'm talking about my G. Everybody calm down.
OK.
I'm going to be watching.
Have fun.
Was that, was that, oh, I love you.
Thank you.
You're interviewing the back?
Love you Spunky. Hey guys Spunky gets like the biggest W of the day because now I'm gonna go to tattoo parlor
I'm gonna get this fake the statue this fucking stupid tattoo that this bitch
It's like he was like before you go make sure your shit's charged
My phone. Oh, you're right shit. Yeah
If you're gonna stream this shit, you got to make sure your shit's charged
Yeah, it's a 28% but that's a really w for you because thank you now. We need at least 80
We need at least 70 or 80 percent
It will charge fast and yeah, I'll get it in a few minutes. I'll get it in a few minutes
But yes, we can watch this clip after this clip. I'll probably
Call the uber. Let me see how long is it? Just it's a little but here's so look at the book is on the panel Michael
Look wheezing on RP. He passed away July last year July 19th. I think we have KZ. I don't know why the fuck
I ever had him up. We have nobody knows why right?
It's a mystery, you know God he always makes shit up. Who's that black RG's on the panel?
So he's dancing to the mystery in the sky. Yeah, and Q can I I want to dance to the mystery with you sometime, okay?
No homo, okay?
We can just be on separate sides of the dance floor, but I'm gonna be looking over at you occasionally
Is that okay with you?
Hello, hello, what?
Thank you. Never mind. Never mind. Just forget it. I said when I left a few days ago
You keep saying be to come back beta. I love you beta this and that I said I love you too
I'm not coming back to the channel because I don't want to bring all that shit in here
I don't want to bring the drama
I don't want to bring all of that and I left I was like, you know behind the scenes
I did give you advice and then you did it again over and over and again
I'm like so I keep it careful and I did I was fine. I was like, you know what you're not fucking listening
Yeah, I'm not gonna sit there and like, listen,
what were you saying when I hung up?
Are you so self-aware to realize that, you know what?
What I'm trying to tell you is best for you?
No, don't fucking bring my name up.
I'm bringing into this.
The way you treated me in summer last night was shit.
You literally put us, you're like, all right, go then.
Bye, get the fuck out.
You too.
And yeah, you did call me a lot of fucking names.
You also said you hated me.
You looked at me and you're like, guess what, Bea?
Guess what?
Bita is going to fucking cry baby bro.
It's so fucking annoying.
And you're my fool.
And then you fucking kick me out like a dog.
Oh she doesn't fucking cry about everything.
I'm not on your being sarcastic.
You can message me like in the early mornings with a bunch of messages.
Bita.
Let's say it was a script.
Shut up.
How am I going to script summer?
How do you want me to cover this shit up for you psyche?
Yeah, we're not covering shit up no more that ship has fucking sound
I'm a real person and I have real fucking issues and I'm really fucked up in the head
So I'm really crazy. So guess what? I don't do fucking strips and I don't do behind-the-scenes shit
It was even going it's ridiculous
You're lame as fuck!
Psyche, Psyche, can I ask you a question?
This isn't a year ago!
I've got a basic idea of myself, what I believe it's about.
It's about an ego at this point. It's about, you know, how many people are viewing how much money is coming in.
He doesn't care about who was there from the beginning or end or equal.
Just, you know, every single one of us has put things out there.
I'm nothing against DJ Electra. I think she's amazing.
But last night you literally said, DJ Electra, you're the only person that was there for me.
I said in the situation with the
And you also said I hate you, Bita
I did not
I did not I don't use that word
Yes, you do when you're drunk somebody clip it somebody clip it
Find that I want to find that. I don't that's not a mother of Cabela
You said
Alexander and Alex dick you ever say that
Well, because I'd seem like why should we go suckin dick you wanted to
Yeah, you want to suck a sick not us. That's my fucking brother. I don't need to suck his dick
You're the one on his fucking nuts and his ass wipe
Wait, why did you ban him?
I'm pretty much done, like, I was like, you know.
I don't want to hear this.
What was your point?
I heard summer up here, and yeah, I'm gonna come up here and fuck him.
Because, like, it wasn't fair.
The reason I even joined last night was because I saw what was being done.
I don't think he was saying that.
He was like, he was shot towards me.
And it also hurt me because I was like, what the fuck?
Like, you know, you didn't want to hear what we have to say.
And you act like a baby.
You're just like, oh, I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear it.
I want this.
I want that.
And it's like you need this you won't see you're turning your back. Just like a baby. This is like you're 45 years old
Fucking man, dude, like what the fuck stop acting like a bitch
We got fucking mumbling the slow one here in the left and right corner
People
Because he knows that I can fix it and he knows that I
I just want to make this is their business
And psyche calls it that's who caused it
I don't, I mean, I don't really know I was in there like from the beginning, but I hold psyche responsible because he needs to be able to, you know, manage and control everything and respect everybody.
I did ask him yesterday, would you have like booted on Alex NYPD.
If it wasn't for the $50 that Tracy provided he said no so to me that tells me he wanted Alex here
He wanted him despite him threatening
He loves that shit totally against he loves it
Psychi this is not a joke if you want to talk get up and have a little bit of respect for me in summer
Because you would do that and I'm all right now you'd be popping up going
Or what's the other girl that he's always fucking talking about none of these people even fuck with him?
That's the fucking thing about it crazy stay out of your mumblemouth douchebag. Let's these three can hear me
You can understand every word I say
No, you sound like you're going to cock in your mouth and it's not just me.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I don't care.
Yeah, I would get a cherry issue of how your parents didn't give you enough tension when you as a fucking child
You know what I'm saying?
Listen, I'm not scared of anybody. All right. I just want to know what is it that you keep putting the input to I want to hear
What psyche has to say did I say I want to hear black RG has to say I said I want to hear what psyche has to say
Why am I fucking scared of anybody?
We were in the middle of a different-
Am I scared of you?
Okay, go ahead.
I'm trying to be as respectful as possible,
and I'm telling you, just let them be.
Everybody, please be quiet.
Bita and Ghost and Summer, the ones that-
I want to say, by the way, I was just talking to DJ Electra,
like, privately their night, and we had a great conversation.
I told her about all the stuff that's going on.
And Bita, the other day, said,
leave DJ Electra alone.
And then they're like, leave Alisa alone.
Literally having a full conversation with Alisa.
I'm in her discord.
I mean, it's like, they're like,
you're stalking women and stuff.
Literally it is fucking insane.
I'm stalking women.
Okay, first of all, my e-bike has been in disrepair
for probably like four months.
I can walk to McDonald's.
That's about it.
Don't I don't I just don't get it and I but they they say I'm crazy, right? Okay
Then had the issue can everybody please just mute up and let us talk ghost is here since he is the person
This is all about can we he fucking talk?
Hey ghost
Hello, that was really aggressive, but hello
So as I told you all that is not Tony's voice, not even close
No, you're not cuz it's not your fight
You
I did. I apologize early in your channel. I was also on your panel earlier. If you're talking about today, I was on your panel.
Everyone just pile up on me.
Okay, everyone hate me. It's fine
Nobody hates you it with you that clearly stated you hate me last night
No, it's like you have you know alcohol that came out or that's how you really feel
But you said and then afterward you were like whoops, and then you covered your mouth. You're like, I love you
I mean like
Well I said oops, I said oops, no diets, no gym. Oh my god. This ice water hack is the craziest thing you're old enough to know that those are emotional manipulation tactics when you say everyone hate me. Don't do that.
And don't say that because he's trying to feed that.
Don't feed him that face. Don't feed him when he says everybody hates me
Let him sit in that shit because obviously we're fucking here because we don't hate you
Duh, that's why we're here
Yeah, I just had a hundred people in the chat
Wow
There you go putting a chat above your friends again psyche
You know having some class and you know
A pilot to your fucking channel is something, uh, psyche, all right, and remember the only reason you're having it because you wanted this kind of fucking bullshit fuck shit, not like peace and fucking tarot card readings, and this and that, this is what you wanted.
I have to agree about she actually
Otherwise we get thrown on the floor. We're trying to be his friend and ghost came up and just resolve all this right now
Because he's sick and then felt like he had oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know it happened
I didn't know what happened already, I apologize.
I didn't know that summer, I apologize, I just said that, I didn't know that.
Stop talking and maybe just listen baby, do you figure that out?
It was never brought up.
Okay, okay, can we go back to our conversation?
Was it ever brought up?
How could that have known?
Yes, it was!
I'm not even three times.
No, it wasn't.
No, you did not tell me, you did not say it once, since I did it on the stand.
You are a fucking hug, so you can stop looking for attention from us!
Why? Why? Why?
You're trying to talk to Psyche!
You're being rude, man.
RG, shut up.
You're being rude. I don't like it.
It shows so much that you're...
It's not about you, RG.
Psyche, maybe if you care about the people that want to resolve this, tell the people that should not be involved to shut the fuck up permanent.
Put them in the back so we can fucking resolve it.
Exactly. Exactly. And I will do that once RG does. RG, you know what?
Psyche, why don't you put everybody besides me, Vita, and Ghost in the back so we can fucking talk?
Yes. One second.
I can't believe I did that.
I knew talk, Psyche.
Sorry.
Yes, you have to talk with us.
Yes, like you do need to talk to them. They're so emotional about it. What are they trying to say?
We're trying to tell you that it's not him. That's why we were emotional about it. Sorry goes. Yeah, exactly
I joined your panel so many times and like
Yeah, it might have something similar. Maybe I don't know I can probably make my it did kind of sound similar
I'm not gonna lie, but I joined your panel like dude for like the past like I don't know how many months like is it a year?
Yeah, I don't even know it's been a while. We've been here
To join summer's panel. Can I mention other YouTube? I've joined plenty of panels, dude
Never once showed my face by the way. That's my thing. I never once showed my face
That's why they call me ghost
I mean that was the whole like stick to it and then I
Showed my face on your panel last night that after I show my face you still came at me like gonna ban me
Oh, I mean, go fuck it. They're not this point. I mean, I'm tired of I'm tired of drama. It's not me
If it was me, I would, you know, I mean, it's not me though. It wasn't me.
I know we're all tired of the drama, huh?
But you came in pretty hard though, like if you're gonna ban someone I mean come on now
I even showed my face. Did I did I did that Danny?
Anybody I really don't
It's called putting backstage and I just imagine it's going to the groom having a little like a water break refreshment
And it's having certain people just think I put you know, please the black or G Michael or back stage right now
They're in the green room having a drink and like you know
This is the show and
So I can have a drink that's why you did it less. Yeah. Yeah
No, because I
I'm not I don't tell you how to run your panels
But have I ever got in there saying hey keep this person up keep this person up you shouldn't have this person up
Yeah, and if you took off the shirt and flirted with you a little bit
Okay, well, you know, it's like probably not but you know, he's on my
Hey, if I pull my strap on I will you strap on on will you like us in? Yes. Can you please do that?
You know, um, I had like Alexander NYPD on the panel many times other
You are and you just sit there quietly. I'm not expecting you to like bottle my war but
Somebody says something about you on the chat like
Gish away kid Tarot. Oh, you're bad. Oh, I don't like this. Oh, I don't like that
You know, I'm bad. I didn't bring it. I'm modern. Yes, because this was saying shit. Like, oh
It's not about that it's about or you forgot that gish actually donated and had a several readings and she's supported too
You know just getting like a little joke, but then you throw jokes at people all the time
Where there's like let's poke this person a little bit
That is a modern chef. That is a mod. If I'm a mod through somebody, I'm gonna, I'm gonna do is sit there and
Remember when you did the same thing to bronze bird you kicked them because you didn't like his opinion
Yes, I know
I don't want you to like just stop flirting with the straight dudes. You're just like, oh kids get out of here. Just get out of here
No, he's not a broken record. He's a straight man that asked you not to hit on him. It's simple
All the avatars
Okay guys, I'm so sorry and hit on an avatar
I can't, you can't even hit on an avatar nowadays.
I'm literally a shirt man.
If I had to ask you not to, then respect that.
But he doesn't have to be here.
He knows it's my shtick and it's a part of my,
it's part of my joke.
I'm sorry.
That's your thing.
I started.
I started on on the beef sector and we had it. I went to the show and I was hitting on this guy in SSI and
The whole chat went wild laughing. It was like it was just a joke and I was like hey
It's kind of like a funny shtick, you know, and no one says oh Howard sir. You're bad because you told the woman
You can
I'm not saying I am I'm saying he's a big inspiration, but it's like
So I have something that's similar though, I do have a show
You're a drug dude on fucking YouTube that blacks out and throws his friends under the bus. Wow
No, go away, you can't keep me. No
Why you can't get those ghosts didn't say it I fucking said it
Yeah
You did this! You don't get to run from it!
You try to run, you run all the time, but talking to me, bro, I ain't trying to hurt you.
I'm sitting right here, I'm sitting right here and talking. I've been here for an hour, 36 minutes,
104 people in the chat. I'm doing this for everybody.
Right now you kick this guy ghost because of like, blame shifting. You really want to do something on me, but then you kick the other guy.
person
Okay, why is everyone screaming
They're calling me dumb dumb
What if I paid you to move out of your house
the fuck oh my god it's a joke i mean it's like it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a joke it's not a
And when I called you, I don't care.
The ghost said he doesn't like it, so you know.
You didn't have to show your butt hole policy, psych.
Let's be real.
Yeah, you're not a worse enemy, though.
Energy, have I seen you?
No one's showing me.
OK, OK, guys, just try it.
Like, guys, this is like a football game.
I know, one hundred subscribers.
Why not?
We get failed on, so no one feels bad for this for you
today.
Take it, take it, take it, you suck it, you suck it,
you get it, you get it.
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
I'm not going to your channel, and you're just going to say,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
And hit on a straight man. Yes. Oh my god. I'm a spin on Ozzy you hit on Ozzy
He his wife was sitting right there next to him and you did that shit cuz you thought it was funny
Literally in the same room with him. Oh my god. Oh the couch with him and you hit on him
Oh my gosh, well guys, you know, it's like a joke. It's not like I'm sitting in I'm
Because that's what you do you run run like mine
He's a try, but you don't feel bad what you did to me last night. I mean, I hate to make it about me
Before anybody came up here, that's why I jumped up because you're out for me. No one likes me
That's me wrong. Oh, poor me.
And look, and look, and look, and look at everybody here.
It doesn't make me cry as much as you do.
You see, they're really shitty at me calling me.
Well, you're fucking bad.
When you call me a bitch like that,
you got what you fucking got.
OK, well, you got that.
You got that.
Are we even?
Because that's where you wanted to bring it,
so this is what the fuck you get.
Are we even?
OK, so at least the wrath of Satan or something like that.
You got it right?
I decided to change our friendship not me when you called me a bitch that changed our friendship
So I don't give a fuck what you talking about
Well, even here last night when I you know, that's why I came up here and fucking went off
Okay
Poor people that don't even like me
They need to respect subbers feelings here. Come on, buddy
By the way guys yeah, because they like watching you get fucking your ass tuned in on that's why they're not here cuz they like you you fucking genius
And they hate me but four people defended me they hate me all four people hated me and they actually
You're gonna be Texan Vita you're gonna be coming over. Where you back at? Where are you guys at? It's funny now?
It's funny. I'm glad I can't wait
Your piece of shit and I hope they take your fucking channel down how about that I thought these friendships
I wouldn't wish that on you but okay go ahead
I don't do it like this
I'm not smiling at you while you're fucking hearty
You're doing it
I'm just saying like you're a kid I make you smile
You know when I was like the cat in the eye felt
You look that you smiled and you came in the camera you're like
I'm I'm fucking evil and you're the fool and then you it wasn't a joke you kicked me
You kicked me
It was
We're little puppets here for you to play around because you want to be dramatic and you
Can you please join
I don't blame DJ Electra. I don't want to be there.
I'm going to be there.
Yeah
Katrina you'll not notice your wrench just leave the chat and never come back. You don't take your wrench
That'll require effort on my part. You know that go to my phone
Now you don't want to spend that that's exactly that's your problem that's your fucking problem because if somebody was out here
I'm not out of line. I'm not out of line. I don't give a fuck. I'm not gonna suck your dick like he does
How dare you tell somebody to show the fuck a face bitch, and you're a goddamn avatar. You're a cartoon
Everybody's telling her
I never I never I never asked this to show his face. He just did
You made me do it
And you don't get up here on fucking panel talk instead of type it in the goddamn chat
Big I think DJ Electra is like, you know, I think she's a really nice person
I think you might have been a misunderstanding and she's apologizing in the chat
Summer, I think, no, I don't give a fuck dude, I'm not, I don't think, I don't think safety should be more in charge and be like, wait a minute, let me figure this out, and let me clear it up.
No, because she's the admin to his page as well.
Summer, how many times did I show my face on your panel, and how many times did I join, uh, zero to, uh-
Coach seems like a really nice guy too, this is a shame.
A hundred times now? I've never once shown my face.
No, but before we look at this one y'all, the one I've seen last night is fucking bullshit.
Well, it's kind of bullying. I'm not gonna lie. I don't suck people's dick just to suck they dick. Sorry, not my thing
I've never came up here and acted like this with you psyche, but that shit last night was fucking ridiculous
Yeah
Nothing's a too, but I had too much to drink. I had too much to smoke. I had too much things going on
I was in my emotions. I was up and down and it's like and I apologize and it's like that's all I can do
I apologize earlier and you laughed about it
You literally kicked me and said oh, he wants an apology. Oh, you literally laughed about it
Because you asked me several times and I already said I apologize early in the show
He asked me for apology. It is trolley. It is trolley me, okay? You're trolling. Everyone's trolleying me.
No, it's hard. We're telling you that you did the shit you did last night was bullshit. It ain't trolley.
Bullshit. I don't like it at all
That's your problem. You think everybody that's telling you shit that you probably need to fucking here cuz last time we all called you dude
We all fucking coddled you
Fuck that dude. I'm not calling a grown-ass fucking man
The only thing I suck is my husband's that's it no one else is so I'm not gonna suck your dick to make you feel good
Amen
Scream whenever the fuck I want you got a problem with that. See what you must want to get screamed at again
No, no, no, please. I like it. Shut the fuck up. I'm not talking to you
Wait till your next talk is show some
People cuz when you piss off the right people we react how the fuck we want see that's the thing
You think y'all can play with people and then when they react y'all when you're crazy. Yeah, bitch. I'm fucking crazy
Well, let's just think she's above everybody with her little
Oh, stop it, RG. That's not true.
It's not.
What about you and your little radio show radio guy?
Fuck this, his lame as fuck.
I'm pausing it once again.
I'm gonna take it down first again.
We have, and this is my last time letting him on.
The next time, if he pisses me off and I kick him off,
it'll be $25.
No questions asked.
What?
You can make money off of me.
Tell people paid you $25 to kick me.
Next time they will.
All right, you go tell them now.
Tell them now.
Give them a chance.
Hey guys, to kick Sam out tonight,
25 bucks, Psyche Awakens Cash at Benmo.
I'll give you my number back stage
if you want to do Benmo.
Let them support you.
They hate me so much.
Let them support you, Psyche.
You know what?
I'm eating my anti-kitty tattoo today, Sam.
Are you gonna watch?
Yeah.
You are?
Oh yeah, you are.
It doesn't mean content for you, right?
We got a concert. Shout out to the concert. Let them pay you. Look, 25.
Hey, Sam, can you cook my butthole, please?
Look, they not going to pay you 25 to kick you? To kick me, I mean?
I don't know if they will, but you know what?
Don't don't they hate me that much, nigga?
I hate you that much. I hate you more than that.
Hmm.
Now what, N-I-G-G-E-R?
Hello?
I think we lost him. I'm here. Oh my gosh. Yeah. All right. What are you counting your Eugeo cards? It's Eugeo
God bless you man. I'm your Pokemon Pokemon. Yeah, Pokemon. I could buy you McDonald's, bro
Hey, can you buy me McDonald's one time?
What what what want to make you like a couple hundred bucks. You can't buy me a big Mac. You're hungry. You hungry papa
You hungry. Yeah, I'm hungry. I'm starving to death. Why water. Why your chapter support you clap me
You know that I just got supported for a hundred
$1,000 tattoo and my Uber rides or it's a God bless. So let's do the content. Okay. Let's do the content
Can I have sex right now? What can I have sex with you, please? Why you see why you being out of here?
Okay, my my uber's on the way six minutes. I'm gonna go wait outside. Yeah
Guys we're going
We're going guys you want a salmon back on oh
Home we have keep my we have we have an awesome person coming up. Let's welcome the beautiful the illustrious the legend
I love you. I love you. Okay.
I'm getting in the Uber in the
lift. It's actually a lift. I'm
getting in one second but um so
I'm going to get it on before I
leave this stream. How are you
today? Good. How are you? Just
good. I'm getting F. U. C. K.
over that that horrible BKG tattoo
I have.
It's fucking awesome. Let's fucking go. Um somebody had a good idea in chat change the um title of your string
What's it should I what should I call it?
Tattoo time
Yeah, or something like that. Yeah
When they're going to come back, but did you see squidy food this morning? He was so cute
He was in the middle of vegas
And there was geese. He touched grass for me
He said he was gonna go gay for me for sure, and I'm okay
I'm the luckiest guy in the world. I know he has a Beatles haircut, and I don't like the Beatles that much, but
Well, the screen must be scheduled in the future within one year. Oh, I'm just oh, I bet you have to do it. Um, I think you have to do it
From the studio once the live is started. Okay. Well, I'm gonna keep it a squeety poo
I know it will scare people away, but hey, this will be
You know trip kick better just better do a recap of this. There's gonna be a panel verse VODs
Sandman's gonna be doing our
Hours of me be between the big troll a lipstick liner and eyeshadow
tutorial
And you know, it's gonna be great guys. We're gonna have so much fun and guys
I'm gonna go get weed to between it. Yeah, guys
This is, I think, the best in my life.
I really do.
You know I got a good times doll?
You see my good times doll?
Yeah, I want to show you one more time.
You're still ugly.
It's cute.
I want to show a gun on your stream.
Can I show a gun?
No, good times.
Here it is.
Get out of my chest.
You're done.
You're done, good times.
You're done forever.
Yeah, we have a good guy.
You like Q, right?
Yeah, I'm all right with you. Okay. That's actually a pretty good good times impression
And I was like oh, this is my cat toy I just got but it looks just like it it really does
Okay, I'm gonna go outside right now. I'll be right back guys
And in Detroit black people call each other the n-word with the hard R
He says that fucking over and over again
And that's not even true either like
And I've been with Mexican drug gangs like literally relax like
What and Gardena I was with the Mexican druggy and our good Arduino are in everything by the end of it
But it let's not forget all about that. I've actually been with Mexican gangs
I don't know if good times was cool enough to be like at the black parties in Detroit
And the college called the n-word. I'm not sure. I'll be right back guys. I'll be right back. Okay. I love you guys so much
So okay, what have you been up to recently?
Shit work. That's about it. You don't fucking work. All right
My bum you're on you're on unemployment. Mm-hmm
Shit, that's what you do
Yep, and you know you you don't make shit. I love how
You know first I already talked shit about you not having a job and now that you have a job
They talked shit about what your job is. I don't understand why that's so crazy
Like what am I supposed to be like the CEO of a fucking million dollar company?
Like yeah, I sell shit door-to-door like and I can make a good amount of money
If shit goes my way if I once I start getting better at the job like I don't understand
Why does it matter?
Like bro, I have a job. I pay my fucking way. I get my own shit. Like I don't know why it's like
Oh, well, it's like it's like if you don't have a car, right?
And people talk shit about you not having a car then you buy a Honda and it's like, oh look at you
You have a Honda like they expect you to buy a Bentley or something like pro acts
Right like they did the vegan when she got her car. Well, that's talking shit about what type of car? Oh fuck
Not that I'm sticking up for vegan, but that's exactly what happened there
This shit just isn't good enough for people on here. They're gonna find something to bitch about.
There's a crazy thing about thing that is
Always has he a thing that is always has shit to say about me in the chat and always talk shit in the chat
But that nigga will never come up here and talk to me face-to-face
It will never happen because he knows I'm just gonna embarrass him and fuck
You know you aren't beat us today you come up here
People and still they're gonna come back. I want to hear what beta said to you day
Tell me how beat is has to do I want to hear your you know my profile picture is thing that is. That's why he's so mad
Yeah, that's thing that is
Is that I thought was Hitler?
No, it's actually the guy that killed good times. It's like a good time. He wasn't even talking about you
He fucked up. He's talking about you talking about you stop it
Hey, look at my car guys. Look at this car
Nice. Oh, that's that's that's funky. That's funky in there.
Hi. Hi, John. Yeah.
How are you today?
Good. We're going to need a tattoo. Let's go.
Thank you.
This guy has a bomb on it.
Like your outfit.
Two.
You look cool.
Don't start.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm kidding. I'm not you. I don't want to get tossed out in the middle of the street. I know I'm just walking around
Okay
We're having a good time. Okay. We're all having a good time
It's like my favorite people some of my favorite people in the world
But you guys hear that stream with summer and beta is like the loudest high-pitched hyena a pack around me
What is going on?
This is why I don't really associate with colored people because you know, it's always
What you
Q I'm about to kick you out of this car stop it
That's what
She's not going to she's not going to
I if you hear you want you want to watch me eat a hot dog. Will that make you feel better?
If you can just shove it down your throat in one bite. Yes, I want to watch it. Oh
damn
Thank you. I
Watch Japanese hot dog eating condos. They can you they can do that's like the cams in a row and they have the biggest
dump in their life
Yeah, I don't want to think about that
Oh, the Japanese know how to eat a hot dog. I'll just say that you know what they eat on Christmas. What are the Japanese?
trivia
Japanese people they get KFC. It's like that's the
KFC is like booked up like months in advance. So the Japanese can have
The drumstick on Christmas, you know that
No, I didn't know that.
The mashed potatoes?
My question is, where are my-
Where are my-
Where are my babies at?
What's your other cat's name?
Luna.
Ginger and you?
Luna means moon in Spanish, right?
I know.
Luna means moon.
Well, I didn't name Luna originally so whenever I was I had them outside
The the kids that live in the apartment complex they named them
I told them to name the cats because I didn't know what to name them. So originally ginger was princess and
Luna was always Luna
You know what you know it if you miss if you arrange the words and ginger do you know the spells?
Oh, yeah, you don't want me to say it though.
Yeah, I mean it's like because some people that restrain me anymore or people that hate me and you know what Kate and I are cool
No, actually we have a secret handshake
It involves we take all each other's palm with our middle fingers and then we like it really turn around and give ourselves like
Like a slap in the hand from from the back from behind. There we go. Yeah, it's awesome
Hey, look here you want to see the streets here remember roll on the window a little bit
Okay, if I roll out the window a little bit back window. Thank you
You're gonna roll out the back window, I think it's not working
Okay, we're on I think oh my gosh. It's actually on my street. It's a I don't I mean not on my street
But it's like very this is like this is where I grew up guys my grandparents
There's like those fat body shop there's Mexican guy that does bodybuilding there
Sometimes I just look at the window and lick the window. Oh, what did I say?
I'm sorry, but Kate you saw that hot that hot muscular guy that it was wearing the scary mask
I hope he goes on the show soon.
I told him, I have a good chat.
I have a bigger chat than he had.
I have a bigger chat than a lot of people on Instagram.
And so, okay, okay, and you're okay.
Yeah, and your shirt is also like twice as big.
It's like, okay.
I mean, we can get these like bodybuilders on our show.
Look, look, forget about the other people.
Bodybuilders in like Jason masks.
Think that's a better idea. All right, let's do it. I want to make you guys know
I don't make all these in drama coming Sam and famous and shit. Look. Yeah, I love those people
I'm sorry. Okay. Looks like I'm annoying. I'm annoying you
You can drop me off if you want
Okay, look like he looks like what she looks like a goddess. He looks like a goddess. Hey, what do you look like?
What kill?
What do you look like you know, I don't know I sound like I used to say this to you all the time
You know what I'm talking about
Right
You look like a bloated body
Peace sign, I'll kick him out. I'll kick him out right away loaded dead body that sounds like Joan Cusack
Yeah, yeah, you definitely do
Has ever watched a movie with fucking Joan Cousack in it, you know that she sounds just like her the fucking principal from school of rock
Well, you know what Kate is cool as fuck and I will mud wrestle in a
I know she's cool, but I mean, as I say, Q, can I mud-wrestle you in a speedo?
Q, would you ever mud-wrestle me first in a speedo for content?
And both of us have speedos on.
Wait, is that it again?
Can we both mud-wrestle in speedos for content sometime?
I am at the tattoo parlor.
Dude, I could grab your fucking head and slam you.
can you please well that doesn't sound nice oh this is a nice but I'm actually
into life fucking captain insane oh thank you for your faces I'm sorry I don't
mean to offend you but thank you so much you have a nice day okay oh my gosh
this lady is speeding away oh my god okay come again come on guy
All right, here we go, here's it, wait, Psyche, full screen yourself, Psyche, full screen
yourself.
Okay.
Here we go, guys.
Do you mind if I full screen?
I'll full screen, huh?
Yeah, go for it.
Okay.
Got it.
Come on.
The worst streamers, we know how this goes.
You got to full screen yourself if you're going to do this shit.
I think you might, I believe in you guys.
Here we go.
Is this it?
I got it.
There you go.
There you go, bud.
Okay, so wait, wait, wait. Don't walk in there with your camera like just facing at them like make it. Don't make it
Oh god, don't
Asked is it backwards? Oh
All right now we're all right. All right, there we go
Here we go. Sorry. Here we go
My god, I feel the awkwardness through the phone
Was the airplane right there, unless you have a better idea of a cool idea
I would say do that or like give me like like a nice script to my house, okay, whatever you want to do
Okay, I don't need your ideas
Guys, they're really really cool here
DKG
This is the place to go. The people were such assholes to me
OK, I'm going to put it on, uh, how do I do this?
You're doing a great job, Psyche.
No, we don't need to be up here.
You need to have yourself on full screen.
Don't have us up here.
Fuck that.
I know, OK.
Hold on.
There we go.
You're the content.
We're just here for moral support.
What's the yeah, we're just adding yeah, we're just adding to the content
This is a historical moment ladies and gentlemen
Fuck be cakey
Wait, thank you. Let me ask you this. Did the artist or did the tattoo artist say that he would be able to replicate the the font?
Yeah, but I said what he said or can you really cool unique script? I said, but everything is best.
I just want to even if it's not even if it's not fucking a hundred percent perfect
It'll still be fucking it's just the way that it was supposed to go. That's the way she goes
Yo psyche you're a fucking legend for this I just want you to know that you're a goddamn legend in this text symbol for this
and the text symbol
damn
I'm gonna fill in my initial
initial
initial initial
initial attack again
and I'm gonna go yes yes yes
yes yes
people, remind us who pack you smoking on
I'm smoking on that fucking
Josephina pack, that caribolo pack
that
big money pack
guys this is my city right here
This is my city. I grew up here. Look at that. That's where I grew up on that hill right there
See that hill right there? See the hill?
I grew up on that hill. That's pretty cool.
This is my city. This is the main street in the city. I walked outside.
I stole their pen. Okay, I'm gonna go back in.
Hey guys, by the way, here is the avenue.
Here is the avenue where we delete fuckin'-
Guys, James is at you, 1305, South PCH, okay?
As soon as you get this tattoo done, I'm sending 50 bags of concrete to beta
Well, I have nothing to do with that me either me either I don't I don't
I can afford maybe like 20 or 30 bags of concrete. After that, that's a little bit crazy.
I finished it. Okay, give me one second. Thank you so much. Okay, I got my ID. I got my ID too.
I want that pillow over here. Make sure you let them know that you're gay.
They know I'm gay already
They might not want to reuse the same needles that they used on you. They're not going to
I'm for great. Thank you so much
She offered me a bottle of water. I'm good. Hey the gate. I already got the decade is
Can you ask her if she squirts
He's part
Guys I haven't fucking luckiest person in the world. I think this sets you
Thank you so much
You guys know spunky she's cool
And guys I got the cute
I had a really cute
are you ready guys I want the chats about what do you think number one or
number two number one number one number one number one looks way better number
one way better number one looks way better
Yeah, you listen you definitely you're you're in you're in good hands that that guy. Yeah, you're good
Yeah, this is what he's doing. I like it
You guys we have 46 I got you just share the live and say psychies like getting attached to saying fuck
BKG on it right now
Everyone get over to psychies right
Listen, if you if you if you promise to fucking bring me back on the stream
I can share it on my you might mark you of course just take off his sweatshirt
Yeah, but you might be too drunk to let me back on stream
I'll remember q I remember you better be stuck in your back. You better you better be checking your backstage. I
Will you you know, I love you. Okay, you're my homie, right?
As long as our bros begin like joke around with each other if you say oh, thank you the faggot and stuff like that
I don't like them behind the scenes.
My feelings will get hurt.
You will be unmodded and I'll probably ban you
from shooting out again.
If you say we're bros right now,
I will have loyalty for you.
What do you say?
Can you just say you're my bro?
Is he still here?
I think he might love to go share it.
He might have left, okay.
That's not a good sign.
No, he wants to go share your life.
He wants to go share your life.
I look like I beat it right now.
I'm just kidding
Remember guys big trolls make them go see I'm Sam and you can learn how to lip liner you can learn your eye makeup. Oh, he's back
Are you here? Yeah, what up? I shared your chair
Did I say I'm your bro and then I got your bro
I shared your stream out.
You want to hear his bro.
Okay, here's my bro.
He's my bro.
Kate, can you do it?
Oh, what?
You're my bro, man.
Do you want to stream?
I already shared it, yes.
I shared it.
Thank you so much.
Okay, we're doing perfect.
We're doing perfect.
FBKG.
I'm gonna get weed next too, I'm gonna walk to the bathroom.
Please tell them we don't want to be fucking white, mommy, fucking whores like Bita and
Christine and Amanda and I and X, fuck em!
I think my phone's about to die too, so the phone really died, I'm gonna have to walk
home without the stream on, it's gonna be a disaster.
I can only get at the 50% before I left.
Is there a way to like turn off the light or something?
Let me see.
Okay.
I'm going to turn off the Wi-Fi.
I just have the mobile data.
Can you laugh?
I'm not talking to you psyche. I'm just cutting a promo
Okay, what do you think my those toes kick what she have oh, she has toes she's a
Toes
Hey
Can you ask me if I ever got my dad's jersey back?
I didn't get my dad's jersey back, but I got my fucking get back. That's for sure
And no guys worth to wear 28% so we're good
Okay ready
Yeah
Let's go
Fuck me KG
Let's take the shirt off
Yeah, I mean you go shirtless and wear fucking speedos on panel you should have no problem doing this here
What's that? What's that necklace coin thing that you wear? What does that say?
The one that looks like a big penny
Bottom one is actually
Guys
I don't know why I'm talking about it.
Is that okay?
Wait, no, no, no. The letters have to be thicker.
The letters have to be thicker.
They have to match the thickness of the letters on the bottom.
Otherwise, it's going to look stupid.
Okay, he'll do it over. Okay?
Just tell them they have to match the thickness of the letters at the bottom the font looks good the font looks great
Now the font looks great it just has to be thicker I got the best guy here
So reality Nancy, he's getting the word fuck over BKG, so it's gonna be fuck BKG
But yeah, it has to be it has to be the same thickness as the BKG letters, otherwise it's gonna look retarded
You just got to add like 30 pounds to that tattoo
Yo, Kate are you still here?
I'm here
Okay
Thank you
You want to see this
Is that your a a coin? Oh never mind
That's that's the fucking that's the iron cross from the Germans. You're a good Nazi. Oh
The big penny
I hope he's in a tattoo that shit thicker than what it is on the outline
because it's going to look crazy if he doesn't.
So it looks stupid.
Just letting you know.
Oh, it'll be all right.
It's not.
It's like a skinny fucking eight.
Do you have any tattoos, Kate?
Yeah.
One, two.
three, four, five, six, six,
you have more tattoos than me.
I only have one, two, three.
I only have four, I think.
I got one on my foot, three on my back,
one on my thumb, one on my hand.
One on your foot.
Yeah, you were definitely a hoe.
I should hurt so bad, so bad.
I know my sister actually got fucking.
uh, Tigger from fucking Winnie the Pooh tattooed on her foot and she literally passed out from the pain when she was getting tattooed.
Like, she fainted because she was in so much pain from it on the top of her foot.
You know what I mean? Like, from, you know, on the top of her foot.
Yeah, that's where mine is and it was awful.
Oh.
Big red balloon says everyone say hi to Christine. She's watching hi Christine. Go fuck yourself old hag
You know what you know what bud I really miss pot hog
Psyche is having a life-changing moment right now, and I think we should all
Be there um shout out to the tattoo artist you're you're a fucking gangster
Our friend Psyche here, um
He's robbed a couple banks
he's been on the run a few times so what you're doing like what you're saying
fuck bkg that's a bank robbing gang bkg is a bank robber gang so psyche has
finally gotten out of the bank robber gang and so now he's changing his life
BKG stands for bank killer gang
Is it hurt in psyche oh, yeah, it hurts. I don't care what anybody says it always fucking hurts
Okay, cool. I'm getting throat go on my next super class.
That's hot. There you go.
There's always this one chick whenever I'm on the YouTube shorts lives,
and she has the words solid tattooed on her throat,
so everyone just calls her solid throat.
And it's like, and it's like solid tattooed in graffiti.
You know what I mean?
Like it's like graffiti style.
So it looks ghetto as fuck.
Shout out to solid thrift.
Whatever her YouTube channel is,
I don't even know what it is.
I just know her as solid thrift.
That's funny
You never go on YouTube shorts lives dude, there's some fucking characters
It's it's crazy. I go down rabbit holes the people like you'll you'll run into some you'll run into also
Like sometimes you'll run into like famous people like the other day I was like scrolling I ran into fucking Ray J
Ray J on the shorts. Yeah. Yeah, Ray J was on it was doing it was on YouTube live shorts. Yeah 100%
Who did I see, um, the, not the cash me outside girl, but the other one, um, uh, well, Vicky, yes, the one that pretends to be black, like, yes, I was like, what the fuck.
Like he's going through a life-changing instance right now. I you know, this is this is really something
This is liberating psyche psyche. This is actually one of the most legendary things that I've seen on YouTube
Fuck Bita. She's a hypocrite a scumbag and a weasel and
I wish I you know, I wish I could have got to you sooner and I could have let you know about this sooner
I, I think I was warned. I think I was warned. I just never listened to anybody.
I'm very stubborn.
Yeah, just like Alex Mayers.
Alex Mayers. How about, how about this for content?
Like that.
How about that? Catch me outside.
How about that?
guys were done already I would only take like 10 minutes it's it's very easy to fucking
do letter you're a fucking you're a fucking you know what you're a fucking you're a punk
star you're a goddamn punk star that's punk raucous
That's punk rock is fuck right there fuck be the fuck BKG fuck Christine fuck all of them
Fuck all of them we used to I remember we we were a community one time
That's why we call good times grams because he was the oldest person now. Everybody's older than good times
I'm younger than you, and I look like 30 years older than you.
What the fuck?
We still call good times Grampson.
He's like the youngest person on panel most of the time.
I know.
He's like 44.
I'm like 45.
I mean, I don't understand.
This is fucking insane, dude.
Can we share here?
Okay, shout out to spunky for the fucking for dropping the donut to get it done
She's probably watching shout the spunky
W spunky W psyche, yeah big dubs all around fuck bkg
I love my driver's license.
Does it burn, Slarky?
Does it burn?
No, I had, like, two, like, great beers beforehand.
No, I mean, does the tattoo burn, Dickhead?
Oh, I thought you meant my butthole. I'm so sorry.
No, wait a second. I'm just kidding.
That was a terrible thing. I'm so sorry.
Where's the ACM?
You know what ACM stands for?
Did they cover it?
They cover it
Yes, yes, yes, I was sent them. I was in the cash, so we're all good
No, I mean like they put something over the tattoo like it's
It's good, um
Like a like a saran wrap on it. Okay one of the ACM. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, just leave that on for like maybe a
day max
This is intercar leaving a slot, but I'm like, oh here. That's the wrong card
My right card. I got
The fuck oh no take it off take it off like the next I got I got I will I got it. I got the card
Guys can't see my pin code
See
Yes, everybody because because Sam-Man has no content
He has a bunch of fucking fruit cakes in his chat that just fucking applaud him and used him as like some stupid little muppet that he is
Yep, there's ever since ever since Sam-Man do shit besides
Troll and then man. You're a little fucking muppet
Hey, psyche. Can you put everybody back on the stage again?
Yes, I can
Thank you, I appreciate that
Same man, you're a fucking loser you fucking clown
Your whole entire stream is based off of other humans not yourself people don't watch you for you people watch you for the fucking drama
dorky content
Yeah, are you talking here?
Oh, Sam and you're not talking to you. We're talking to fucking Samuel Torres
Okay, hold on a second. Oh
Yeah, he's really rich because he made fucking he makes $25 for kicking somebody, you know, it's crazy
To where I'm at now and me and same man still have the same thing
Nothing like he don't have no car. He don't have no house. He don't have no family
Me and you were in the same position and you're almost 20 years older than I am
No, no, not 20 year you're like 10 years older than I am. Sorry you have nothing in your life
You the only thing that you have is your little fucking stupid dorky YouTube stream. Oh my god
I I get 90 viewers on my YouTube stream. I'm really successful. I'm a really big deal around here
He lives for this internet shit. It's all he has in life lives for it. That's all he has
crazy
Okay, I'm having a problem
Like wow, it's so hard to get a hundred viewers whenever you stick your nose in every little piece of drama that happens in
Every fucking corner of YouTube
Wow
You literally just aren't you all he did was hijacked Zaya's community. That's really all that happened
I might have to go to the supermarket for this one.
Uh-oh.
I have it actually.
Yo, Gaudi, I remember when you were on JC Stream
and you admitted to being bi-curious.
You remember that?
So shut your whole mouth.
Gaudi's bi-curious? Damn.
Gaudi, are you in a wheelchair?
Is that true?
It's quite curious. I'm not judging. I'm just saying like don't sit up here and talk shit like you're the one you're a fucking clown
Now he's calling me a queer. Now we're projecting. You see how this goes? You see how this shit works?
Oh, damn. I'm just trying to sit here drinking my blood water.
It's about to be Easter Sunday and you have all this hate in your heart.
Jesus resurrected. Okay, I need to go to another store.
market like Spartan final and do it full transactions just right look this right
down the street and I know all the I know all the real estate around here
because can you can you run there can you run there
they do a little jog and you run before that there you go yeah run
What's the ATM that works?
He's actually running. No, it's like it's like it will let me take out cash and stuff but the ATM won't because
It's that like a certain amount, but I can like take out $100 past like zero
Then put the other stuff in my cash app, but I own cash and some money
What up Eldo thought the elder
I'll be Kate. Are you cool with elbow these days or you guys still at odds?
I was asking I was asking Kate if she was cool with elbow these days or if you were still at odds
No, Q. I want to ask you something
Yo, you right now motherfucker. Oh words like that asshole
Well, he was trying to get an answer out of me. Oh my bad. No, not really not really cute. I'm not
So y'all I pretend he doesn't exist. All right, that's all what's up? Let's
Yo, I want to ask you you got on that link somebody posted a picture of somebody
What
Somebody told me you got a link a link of somebody posting a picture of somebody
A link of somebody posting what a picture a picture a picture of her what?
Well, what it's not what it ain't you know, it's a fat a fat person. Oh
That's me. I got that you know, I'm not so much the girl
I'm not sure what we're going on. I'm not sure
I'm not really involved
Well, you think that I have a picture of Amanda. I've never even spoken to that one.
I do. Nah, that's what's on my phone.
Oh, I got it. It's on my community post.
I don't even talk about that woman. I don't, I don't even,
but I've never even spoken to that chick.
I've got the clip where it happened, too.
Yo, Kate, we can't hear you, Kate.
You can't hear me?
Shit you can we can hear you we can hear you we can hear you that's can't you're not me. I'm talking about Kate
We can hear both of you everybody's
Oh
She was like I didn't hear her that good. I don't think less can hear me because of the I
Probably got a leave and rejoin
No, you're good you have perfect
No, he know everybody can hear you
Less can you hear tape? No, I can't hear
That's what I say. All right. Well, let's you got to leave and rejoin
No, no, no, because this is like a thing that's been going on in stream yards lately
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with their shit, but this is happening to a lot of people
Wow
Some people can hear other people in the stream yards and shit, it's all fucked up
Now I need to pee really bad
I'll be right back. I'll be right back cuz I did this also happened to Kate the other day, too
I remember Kate was like I Kate you couldn't hear Benny when you joined fucking like he's panel
right
But I think it has to do with like who was here first whenever the person
I didn't see it the bathroom should
Down stop running psyche stop running calm down now. I'll make you have to pee even here. I'm actually here. I'm here
Bro you're in California just piss anywhere nobody cares homeless people piss everywhere all the time
I mean, that's the noble and that's the white thing to do, you know, it's mind the white of you
Thank you so much guys imagine me myself cuz I don't want you to hear me pee. Yeah, turn your camera off, too
What the fuck is his picture I was as the dog you don't even have a dog
Who's fucking dog is that okay? Okay, psyche is getting his tattoo fixed. It now says fuck
BKG
Yeah, yeah, that's that's the whole reason why how many viewers are there there's probably like what a hundred people here
Yeah, psyche just got his tattoo fucking fixed. How many people are here?
Cry man is restreaming. So, you know, oh, oh, yeah, so there's way more people here. Oh
for sure
Yo cry man why are like the gene pool of your family is like so bad everybody in your family is so fucking ugly
That's what I'm trying to figure out
Your sister and your mother resemble Shrek
They're fucking honestly it looks like somebody like it looks like his mother fucked his
Cousiners or his mother fucked her cousin or something like they had some sort of like
Inbred something that happened in Samans family because they are fucking disgusting looking human beings
They look like if if if if if everybody
Resembled sake that's what his family his sister literally looks like the female sake
Them people are ugly as fuck
That's like you go phase right there
Nobody even was talking about Samann or brought him up until motherfuckers came in here and we're talking about that
He's restreaming this panel like nothing had to do with him at all
No, so no, this isn't an I hate Samann panel Victoria. Why don't you go to act of Samann's chat you stupid bitch?
Troy are you causing problems? Okay, stop it
Most of the people in same-man's family have underbites
Hey, I'm gonna get one of these. You're good. You're called the shit noodles
Go get you a can of Chef Boyardee nigga. I
Don't see the Chef Boyardee, but how about a Rosarita and fried beans?
Spicy jalapeno. Hell yeah
Do it
I like makes I like makes if you want the if you want the best cheat meal
Just go get a fucking a box of pasta and a can or a
Like a bottle of fucking spaghetti sauce, and that's like a solid ass meal for cheap as fuck
These lines are so long and then that you borrowers you've never been poor before
I have actually, I spent one night with homeless people on the streets.
Yeah, it's like the most awful thing.
I went to the next day, I had chiggers bites on my leg, all over them, and it's cute.
No, no racial jokes, please.
I don't know, what are you talking about?
You just think so.
You just honestly, you think so fucking rotten of me.
I don't.
I love you.
I'll go with you.
I love you. I mean, part of that is what I love about you.
Part of that makes me a little bit scared
that I wouldn't survive at night.
But, hey.
Gotti says, can you spend a weekend...
Okay.
A live stream at a grocery store
and no pranks or shenanigans?
Sirs, can you wait for the camera?
You're on YouTube Live.
Just wave. Just wave. Hi, guys.
That's shenanigans, they're the kind of shenanigans
Try my best guys. I'm trying my best. This is one of the long hair roots of neo-nazi
It's a woman
Oh, I think you're talking about me
Sorry, sir. Yeah, I was talking about you
This isn't this is awkward awkward
Awkward in my life. I just start doing like the the robot dance. I feel sillier than Tommy jane. They're calling security on me
Thank you so much, sir. Thank you appreciate it
Cancel that cuz he knows I'm like
Thank God
Yeah, it's like yeah, I wish you could have been a part of this community before like all the black people came around
It was so much fun
And all the black people came around and they have all their like morals the periodic shit
Q. Do you know OJ Simpson might be standing behind me with a knife? Why are you saying those kind of things? This is terrible
OJ Simpson's dead, isn't he? A lot of black people agree with me. Oh, yeah, he did die, but that'd be even scary. He'd be like a zombie
Hey, you have to see how tall my cashier is. He is like, I'm 6 foot 3. This guy is like 7 foot tall, I think
He's smiling. Hold on. Look at how tall this guy is
Tall drink of water
I don't know.
Oh, he looks.
He is tall.
Tyrone.
Call Tyrone.
Call.
And tell him come over.
Come get his shit.
You could just call on Tyrone.
Ericka Badu. Ericka Badu. Oh, do you mind if I film your dog for a second? She said she doesn't want me to film her dog. Your dog's a camera shy?
No, film the dog. Film the dog. I want to know what the dog's name is. She can't stop us from filming the dog.
The dog said it was a fake.
That's an ugly ass dog.
Yes, yes, yes. It's cute though. I love them. I love them. I love dogs.
I do a lot of annoying cats are way better.
Mine is sitting right here.
We're now annoying, bro.
Isn't she?
Well, yeah, low like a girl.
Like when you buy a dog, it's like, uh, it's like, you have
to deal with a retarded autistic child for like eight years or 10 years.
Yep.
That's okay.
I'm 6'3".
No, it's not.
You're 6'9".
Yeah.
I'm 6'3".
Wow, this guy is...
That's funny.
Hey, okay.
Stikey loves 6'9".
Okay.
Can I use your transactions and $50 each?
Yeah, just take up one and then I'll do 50 or 50 plus the thing and then 50 plus
the thing.
Is it a debit card?
Yes.
you want to make sure make sure you check the name on that debit card because it
might not be the same name as him you might want to look at his ID it says
Q45 on it is that my name yes it is okay thank you know your name is fucking
Is it 50 damn that dog is ugly as fuck
Yo
Jerk
Okay, guys, it's work ever that dog looks like it's
Okay, we're doing one more transaction
That dog looks like it's my cigars, okay
You don't smoke
Girl she just a hot mess she needs to go to the groomer the PCM. No, she don't need a bath
I'm very specific with dogs. I only like very like certain breeds like a lot of them
I just want to thank you and I want to say that you're talking to me but they're fucking
youthless.
You're welcome.
Okay.
I'm out of here.
We're talking.
Let's get back to the tattoo parlor.
He wasn't tall like in water.
He didn't appreciate it.
Okay.
But I'm not all insane.
I mean, I'm crazy.
But I'm crazy like a fox.
Yeah.
Maybe a fox.
Maybe you're a fox.
the
Where they cool everyone is so nice. Why are they nice to me? I'm like the worst person in the world. I
Don't get it
But when I get back there in my ID and giving them money and some no tip
Know it's like you that's one of the great things. I love about being white is like most people are fucking nice to you because you're white
You know, they just don't expect anything, you know, they don't expect any hostility in the first place
That'd be like we're like when niggers talking niggers
When these blacks talk to people, it's a whole different ball game
I'm sorry guys
The sky looks the same there as it does here
Guys that's a terrible joke. I mean, I'm only fucking I'm in San Bernardino. I'm not that far
Did he come over tonight and hang out with me?
No.
Why not?
Not that far.
Because I might fucking, I might choke your fucking windpipe and say you can't breathe anymore.
That's my fetish.
Cue, that's my fetish.
I love being choked.
You know that?
And you spit in my mouth at the same time?
Do you like being punched in the face?
Cue.
What, that bitch?
they're going to smack you in the ass, and then eff you.
I'm like a foot taller than you.
I could grab you and throw you like a football.
You're one inch taller than me, nigger.
I'm six foot three.
Hey, hey, hey, don't say the N word.
That's wrong.
No one cared.
I don't even around.
All right, you dirty nigger.
Yeah, let's not say.
Well, he said it.
You didn't care when he said it.
I did something over you.
I'm white.
I think honestly that I think it's better that we normalize that word because then nobody's gonna care about it, right?
If if I if I call psyche like hey psyche, you're a nigger like you're white though
It doesn't even matter. You're a white guy who cares I
Think he froze like yeah, I'm gonna care. Well, I think we should normalize calling everybody and words
Um, Mexicans, white people, black people, there are niggers in all cultures.
But you, for once I agree with you.
What, am I here?
Yeah, you're here.
We can hear you.
Okay.
Okay, good.
Yeah, for once, no, not for once I agree with you.
Actually, this is, okay, this, okay, guys, do you want to see the coolest place?
Hold on.
This is like the, it's called the Joseph Alberry Salon.
Been here forever, as long as I can remember.
Back stage, I can't believe I did this.
Look at the salon.
You know why it's so iconic?
I need to say one thing.
So when we say that shit, when we say that shit, Kate,
I understand, you know.
I without saying too much. I understand why that shit affects you the way that it does
We say that shit in dramatic effect like it's not nobody gives a fuck about actually fucking
Oh, yeah, I hate black people whatever like nobody cares
but
I can't be racist if I think that the more I think the more that word is said it would be like
I didn't like that slavery everything I think it I think it should be like how we toss around the
word faggot like it should be the same thing with the n-word like like nowadays nobody cares about
saying faggot oh well he's gone I think you had to go in and pay it
And then he um
Think he's got a book is uber home, too
You can't believe he really got it. That's awesome. I need to get a tattoo covered up
I'm my ex is gonna remind everybody that this is my idea in the first place
And it actually came to fruition for once shout out
I really do wish though that he would have got the fucking font thicker because it like the fuck is kind of skinny and
BKG is thick
That's the only problem. I I told him you got to get the same thickness
Hang on listen to it and we're
Yeah, they let him they his card wasn't working or no he didn't have his ID to go with this card
So he had to leave to go get cash
I'm inspired
This probably shouldn't be the situation to get inspired
This is not it. I want to get a cover-up
Well, if you do get a cover-up though make sure
There's certain artists that like specialize in cover-ups and they do like but great jobs
I'm sure you can find you don't live in like the absolute middle of nowhere. You could probably find one
Well, I do live in the middle of nowhere, but I'd have to travel. Yeah, well, you're close enough to like the moon
You're not
You're not far away from civilization. You don't live in the fucking bayou or nothing. No
Hi, Lisa
Lisa who Lisa Stewart, I know I don't Lisa. I'm not sure. No, that's not Lisa Stewart
No, that's not Lisa Stewart. Um, I'm not sure which Lisa that is
Fuck that Lisa I don't care about Lisa Stewart
No
Yo, you know it's crazy. I had a dream the other night
Because a
Couple of years ago when I was living with my uncle. I joined your panel when I was like at the bar and
I had like a fucking weird deja vu dream about that shit. It was so fucking strange
Like I was on panel talking to you and some other fucker
Who else
I can't remember I know it wasn't just you though because it was like multiple people were like yelling at me like like like say it like calling me a fuck like a fuck tar like
obviously I know that's not how it went but I do remember that time because I remember sitting outside of the bar and being on your panel when I was
And this is like right after that,
like I had like just joined your panel.
Like just started joining your panel again.
And I'm like sitting there on like the fucking,
on the stoop or whatever,
and I just like see like traffic going by.
And I'm like on your panel, it's a weird ass dream.
It was so weird.
But I remember like, I know why I had that dream,
because
I like experienced that type of thing in real life, but it was just like exaggerated in the dream
That's crazy
Where it feels like deja vu
I'm sure a lot of people on
Let that that are streamers or people that watch streams. I'm
I'm sure a lot of you have had fucking dreams about these panels and like
She had about like that is about it. You know what I mean? Especially when you fall asleep and you listen to this shit
Yeah, yeah, 75 dollars and he's like that's fine. That's fine. That's fine. Nice. I
Got a goodness. I think it's worth it
I think it was like kind of way overcharged even a hundred bucks. It's like just for that lettering. I think like 10 minutes
He was so quick. It was really quick
But hey, shout out to that guy.
She's a guy that's at you Farler.
Go to there if you're at Redondo Beach.
You can come hang out with me.
We can like, I won't try to do anything to you
except we can even a snuggle on my couch
to watch Carolus K and talk to you on the stream.
It's all good.
That's awesome.
And you think that other place was gonna charge you 150?
Oh, yeah, let's see the tattoo. Let's see the tattoo for a hundred by like remote the show. Well, and I was like, is that the best tattoo artist you have?
Well, it's the only one we have
Fuck you
We can't even like say that tattoo artist is the best. Hey guys, everyone they don't look at me like
They're like, we thought you just get a big idea and you're gone and stuff like they all they're like, they're happy to get
They thought I fucking ripped them off.
I wouldn't.
I thought I'd be there.
They got it back.
Did you know that thing that is, is a gay man?
No, he's not gay.
He is all man.
He would have had sex with Vita.
He gives me a lot of gay ass vibes for sure.
He loves Vita.
Okay.
So I've been to these brothers on Instagram
and I thought it was a thing that is
that I stick with them.
Yeah, a lot of their guys have girl best friends.
Yeah, they're called faggags.
that's what it is oh yeah that's what they're called they call themselves faggag
faggag so yeah be it as a faggag okay i don't think she is because she like he hates gay people
i don't know what she's got i mean i have as gay as they get i really am but someone was like i've
Yeah, I had to deal with beat up and fucking Christine and summer and
You know what I've been through of course. I mean I
Wasn't it would have eaten me alive like a
Drumstick a lot of your troubles a lot of your troubles on YouTube are because of colored folk
I think you should stay around white people more
Well, I don't I like I'm attracted to Mexicans
We don't want any of these colored folks around.
I mean, up to the right black guy, oh, oh, I can.
I know, I had the black, I don't know.
And I had this black guy, I went on some website once,
and he was like really hot, like really straight acting
and stuff, and he was like a bitch.
He was tellin' the reality Nancy.
Reality Nancy, I love you motherfucker.
Hey Nancy, guys, look what I got today.
Yeah
24 and there's so much more
What time is it? What time is that in fucking the middle of nowhere, Kate?
Seven o'clock.
Oh, so you're two hours ahead.
Yup.
I didn't see anybody walking by.
Fuck BKG!
And the other side of me, I'm going to get a duck, because I'm in the-
Listen, Stygie, that shit was fucking absolutely legendary.
You're an absolute fucking gangster.
You're a celebrity, a sex symbol, all of the above.
Like I said, you know, I'm just me, and it's like, I just been me.
I did have a psychic reading when I was like, probably 10 years or 11 or 12 years old.
And the guy's like, you're going to be on the camera?
You're gonna be like almost famous or something
I just see like people watching all the time and then I was like that's impossible
Even if it's like 40 people compared to like a million people like with a you know, Julia Roberts or whatever
I'm happy with
You know RG RG get your ass up here RG
You like you guys
No, it does look good. I
Wish they would have did a little bit thicker though, but that can always be adjusted. You can always get a thicker. That's no
Yeah, yeah, some I think it's fine. It's fine for now. Maybe you said it will like
They also like they gave me like a huge like discount, I think they like like me and stuff
That was a rip-off and so I would I'm like I'm an honest person
I also got my soups. I got my beans. I'm gonna be get on food for a while
Hey, listen, this is this is what happens cuz you know, we were me and psyche last night
We were talking about like, you know, you know fuck beta beta is a fucking dumbass
And we were thinking about how we could adjust the tattoo, and I said, well, why don't you just get the word fuck over BKG, and it would just be the tattoo just like fuck BKG, and that's where this this idea spawned from and then today I brought it up again and now psyche has something on his body that he can never get rid of.
Well guys
Now we're getting fish chakas. Oh my god, this is like a fever dream. This is like a
I can't
We're getting fish tacos, like what's the next leg or man?
I'm proud of you psyche get them fish tacos and word
Are you still here catered it I fucking I'm here here. Oh so psyche psyche
Yeah, he walked out. He's
He's getting his fish tacos
My question is
Alexander McCoy, where is Alexander McQueen at?
You need to get your fucking punk ass up here Alexander McQueen seen him in a couple days
No, he's
Tilapia tacos. I don't think tilapia is a real fish. I think that's like some government shit
Like they created that fish because like all of a sudden people started eating tilapia out of nowhere like that
It is it's it's uh
What or is it farmed fish
It's not a real tilapia is not real fucking fish
Tilapia is like, it's like the fish that's sold to poor people to make them feel like
they're eating something that rich people eat.
Tilapia, yeah, it's like a white fish, you know, even catfish, people think, oh, catfish
sounds good.
It's like, I actually got a scum-feeding fish, it's not very good.
Maui, Maui.
Yeah, what's your, what's the Uber driver's name?
What's your name, sir?
Andres.
Yo, Andrea, he's cool. He's cool. He's fun. You wait for me. This guy's a bomb. Yeah, this guy has a bomb stop
Yeah, thank you
Q I don't want to be left in the middle of the city with my phone at 1% okay. I just can't do it
I am the bomb
Kate what am I we're in you with this guy
I mean, it wasn't for his looks, I don't want to say what would happen he is
Yes
I mean at least imagine how at the point I should be at. I should be like in
Joker makeup you know running around doing horrible things. I'm still basically a
good person. I still have some of my looks. Maybe 40% is not as good as I look.
Cue you better stop it. I almost got jumped on the side of the road.
I'm sorry I'm sorry okay okay I don't have one literally one percent of my phone
in the middle of the city I know the city well and stuff I could probably find a ride but
I'm actually right at my you'll be good you're almost at home you'll be good
Do IRL with me?
How much money are you, how much money are you paying me?
I'll buy you fish tacos and I'll leave some in my bed
and I'll sleep on the couch and I will touch you at all for you.
And my bed is clean too.
Hey, there's lemonade Seattle.
I'll show you.
That's weird.
Okay.
There's lemonade Seattle before.
Oh, like,
more selling lemonade.
Hey, look, he's born as an eliminated person right now.
Are you going to eliminate me? Are you keeping my mouth?
Is that what you mean?
Ew!
Oh, God.
What's the call with somebody peeing in your mouth?
You would do that, I bet, for like, someone donated five...
You won't piss in your mouth, Edward?
Yeah.
You'd do that?
Yeah, we'd share the money with you though.
Where are my kiddies at? I want to see my kiddies
Kiddie babies
Wow, they're not be
Eliminate eliminate shower for me. Where the fuck are my cats? My bed will still be empty
Q Q you have to let them come to you. You can't yell
They need to be fucking front and center. I need to see Jen. I hide under the bed
In the bed
Look in the cabinets. They go in the cabinets. They go, you know, here's what about cats
They'll go under the couch. They'll go inside the couch sometime. They'll like
They go everywhere
in the apartment
I know ginger is way bigger than Luna, way bigger.
But you can even see it from like this angle.
I'm running in liquor store.
I'm going to take a little more drinks.
I'm going to go back.
Okay guys.
Cool guy.
I swear.
Look at the kitty.
There's a kitty.
You see the Kelly on TV?
Hi sir. Hey, can you see how you're on YouTube?
Happy. Happy Easter day.
Happy Easter.
It's Easter Sunday. He's very nice. He's very nice.
I'm going to get a couple Smirnoff ice,
and I'm going to get another heart of lemonade.
There we go.
I'm always here. He knows me. I'm regular, right?
Yeah.
All right, I know yeah, yeah, I'm good on cigars. I just say alcohol. Yeah
Look at that fucking tail. Oh my god
Thank you, your tail is longer than your body, ginger. Thank you
Happy happy. He's so nice. He's so nice
Thank you appreciate you
You're at your star
Actually, you're literally sorry
Bro, you know what yesterday the fucking whole apartment flooded like there was two inches of water
Throughout the whole apartment two inches that sounds like that sounds like the size of six
Okay, I just show up my wallet again
What woman oh my god look at ginger. Oh, I want one
But I want one just like ginger with the giant fluffy cat a fluffy tail I
Didn't know she was gonna look like that. I just just so happened to stumble upon a kitty
Oh, my God, look at the size difference.
It's fucking crazy.
And they eat the same.
Like I feed them both at the same time all the time, like they don't.
Ginger, just they ever fucking.
They don't really fight.
They play, you know, they mean like they'll play around and wrestle around with each other,
but they don't like his at each other or.
Don't give violent with each other
Ginger looks like a Maine Coon I
Know I actually had the other like I think it was like a week ago
I looked up what a Maine Coon looked like because I thought that ginger might be a Maine Coon
But she's not she doesn't have her he he ginger is a boy
He doesn't have the same face as a main kundas. He's just he's just a big-ass cat
He's only they were born in
September of last year, so they're not even fully grown yet
Like gender is gonna be a fucking monster I
Mean look at him compared to my fucking hand and then look at
and then there's Luna little petite Luna I know that's who's back
let Luna eat that Luna ginger always ginger's always trying to eat Luna's
food oh Luna look at Luna that's a little order there's the other Lola
Can I see the cat in the back?
Oh, Lola, that's Cat Lola.
Cat Lola, too.
Lola, how would you like to date?
Do you want to date a dog?
Name a little, it's another woman, but it's OK.
We're just a person.
You mean lesbian, cat, cat, and dog?
Right?
You ever see that show cat dog. That's what that's what that's having. Hey guys
I wanna go look in the mirror. I wanna go look in the mirror, but I know I'll put it on
Oh, yeah, you haven't seen it. Like honestly ginger acts more like a dog than a cat
But oh my it's all bloody and stuff
Look at that little tail. Oh my gosh
Look at that little raccoon tail.
Hey, I wish I could show you my cat named Freya.
And Freya was like the little fluffy cat of the mix.
And her tail was like humongous.
And she would just climb trees.
She was like a literal, I think she might have been half raccoon.
Is it Scotch-shaped?
No, I think it's some kind of like cat chew cover-up kind of thing.
But it's like, it's hard to see, but I did have like the,
it's covered up, you'll see it when, you'll see it soon.
You'll see it soon.
It looks a little horrible right now, but it says.
Fuck the KG.
Yeah.
There you go.
There you go, Bea.
For all the jokes, for all the, I'm so lame,
I'm so stupid, I'm gonna have that forever,
I'm gonna look at that forever.
Now I look at it and smile and laugh and think,
hey, I'm a fucking G.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm gonna play by Kalyne.
The vibes we could do.
Let me count my money and stuff and make sure I got my all my IDs and my credit cards
And then if I do that's a W for the day. Yeah got my credit card got my ID
Got some extra cash got the cigars got my alcohol got my lighter
Do I have extra cash? Look at this five. Oh my god. I have $30 extra
Thank you. That's a cool place there. She's like, that's fine. I've seen like that's fine
If they thought I was gonna rip them off and stuff. They thought I was like I just left I got my
I even got this like something from chewy. I was on a dead mouse from like that was just sent to me for like a joke
What's from chewy?
Better not be a dead mouse
It is
I don't know what that is.
For a lot of shoes. I think it's
for a dog. I'll just leave it
on somebody's. Give us food. I
don't know what that is. Let me
see.
It's for a dog. It's for buzz.
A dog. I think it's misdelivered.
It was misdelivered. I'm just
gonna put it back in the mailbox.
It looks like a prescription.
Says it kills fleas for dogs.
That's the name on it. So it was this delivery. It's been there for like at least like three weeks.
Well, hi, kitty. Not you, kitty. Not you, bubby. I was talking to the kitty.
All the kitties.
And then there's Lolo the puppy
Zinger's over there under the table cleaning himself
Hey
Hey, that was a successful
Fuckin mission take it to the local post office. I mean, it's like
Somebody that doesn't live here and it's like it's like a number that doesn't even like really
Exists it's like a number off
Yeah, hey, there you go clumsy. I mean, I got a deal with you today. Oh
You know what? You know what one of the thing you know one of the craziest things about clumsy is what?
He's very clumsy
Yes, oh
So crazy
Because oh my god, I secretly use Q's leg
Okay, why is there penis sticking out the end of your shorts?
It's that big
My penis? Relax, dude.
Oh, okay. Oh, that's just a shout-out.
Calm down. Calm down.
Oh, that was your finger. It was your finger. It was your finger. It was just your finger.
Can I touch it, Q?
The finger? Or the leg? Or the penis?
The penis.
Oh.
Oh!
All of them. I want to touch all of them.
Okay, I'm sorry that was too I went too far again. I'm so sorry
Hey, I think reality Nancy is a joke. I can take a dick. He could take a joke
That's what part of being gay is fun in this community. I mean only a gay person here might as well have some fun
Nobody's gonna touch me
Okay, okay, are you sure you said stop with your laughing so hard. Okay, that's good
Like stop and then slap me there. I like that. I like that. That's funny
You see my good time doll. I got a doll of good times. You see this
That's my good time doll
It's him down to the skinny arms and everything you're a nigger. Hey bad doll. I just read the window
We're just went out the window. Fuck. No, uh, I'm a danger. Come here. Okay. My windows are open right there
I just went through at the window. Oh
Good times. That's what you get for saying the n-word on my shit. Oh fuck. Why can't you control yourself?
Good times. Ghosts miss it all. I mean we had some people miss it all and stuff, but
You know, that's what the replay is for. That's what it's for. I mean, can you believe like summer
beta
Exiled one. We're your friends. Oh, you're hurting our feelings.
Okay, where are they now? They're all talking about me on B's bed. I was saying I'm a piece of shit with dirty nails and
Alexander's over here letting me smack his ass and he buy them in McDonald's. I mean, what the fuck?
You do have dirty nails, but you're not a piece of shit
Thank you. I mean my nails. I did kind of clean them up. They're not that horrible. They're not horrible
You have to say they're not like just like let's say a lot of people a lot of people around these communities like
Listen, can you listen to me? Can you listen to me for a second?
Yeah, I'm concentrate on your leg right there. I see the little bit of white though like the whites. Oh my god
Here you can concentrate on ginger. Oh
I didn't see the deer
It doesn't really matter what you do around here.
A lot of people create a lot of false outrage
about a lot of things just because they wanna stir up drama.
Honestly, nobody really cares about anything
as long as you're not a PDF.
Right, but when I create a film, I'm outraged.
They're nobody cares.
Oh my God, thank you, sister Victor.
And I'm joking.
And it's like, and then it's like, but then it goes,
I said the N word, literally for the last like two weeks,
it's been like a scandal.
I'm about to be a national inquire.
Samman says it about 50 times in one minute.
And it's like no one blinks an eye.
I didn't see the Dear John video, but I did see Kate.
Did you hear about this new video of me?
No, what?
Kate, can you go to ip2wiki.info on YouTube
and look at the shorts and look at the latest short,
if you can.
No, I could do wiki info you just search and then just look at the shorts
Hi Luna, oh shut up ha ha no
Right, what do you see this is glad we you see I can't show it, but this is probably you see
I
Tell me James and I
We're having sex tell me you're having sex on film idea. I don't remember that
What do you do when I was asleep? I don't know I slept that deeply. I'm I'm obviously
Yeah, isn't that crazy cake you believe that shit
Q can I put my mouth around your finger, please?
You know a cue spell finger backwards
Stream over that somewhere in there
We see the chat. Yeah, but it's a little bit covered in stuff. You can see the chat. I know Q fuck BKG
It does fuck BKG
So that's what I hear fuck BKG ginger ginger is not a part of beatest kiddies gang
Luna Luna, I don't know yet
And like, and like Bita was like, oh, you can't eat psyche things he can like, you know, like wrangle me and I was like, I'd rather wrangle a like a rabid skunk. And then she goes, he's calling my cats a rabid.
These are they have rabies, and then they look like a skunk because they're black and white. I was like, I was saying that about yeah, not about your cat.
Yeah, I swear to God. Yes.
She got you you said you'd rather wrangle a rabid skunk
Yeah, and she took that as you were calling her cat
Yeah, yeah, well wait the crazy thing though is that I've called her cat skunks multiple times and she never has given a fuck
She's a it's selective outrage psyche. That's that's all it is. Nobody actually cares about any of that shit
They're just electively outreaching on you for content
Every little thing I do is like wrong everything she literally does the clapping system now
How dare you clap someone? That's how do you put someone backstage? Does she like do that a hundred times a day?
Yes, but when I did it and then she tells me to put back saying do not do it's a problem. I don't understand
It's called
Mindfuckery too. It's not very it's not very good mindfuckery, but it's like
I was Luna. Can you not try to climb up? Can you not try to climb up that please?
I'm gonna try to climb up a cue. No, I'm talking
It's just being an asshole right now. Sorry. I'm sorry, and there's there's ginger. I love you
Baby, hey guys, we had fun today. I'm gonna put my my link back up if you want to come
Cating cute guys. Well, you're late. You're late. Not uh, you're late. It's not pinned in the
But no one's yeah, come on up
There's Link again in case you didn't see it. Look at her. She's fucking climbing up the goddamn couch. Oh my god. Uh-oh
Can you relax?
Uh, how do I do this?
Look at what you're doing, brother.
Link is scratching post. Yeah
Look at what I have, I have this, I have this.
Or a cat tree.
You know what?
Actually, the crazy thing is, this hole right here is created by them and they like to sleep
up in here sometimes.
Oh, shut up.
What?
What's wrong with you?
So, honestly, oh, look, she's climbing, she's climbing, she's getting higher.
That's all looking at it, okay.
She's climbing up.
Look at her.
There she goes.
Don't go, girl.
No, no, I'm going to put up this here.
Get up there.
Uh, this, this couch, uh, or this little futon goofy thing, we don't
even care about it anymore.
It's honestly, honest way to the garbage.
So they can fuck it up all they want.
But yeah, this hole was created by them and they were like sleeping up in here,
like up inside the bottom.
I was literally, I brought my cat to a different house and then I was like, he ran away.
And then like literally two days later like I have to like hearing something two days later
He crawled out from inside the couch where he was like inside the cat
It's he like Claude. He went under the couch, which is very like this much space. Oh
Like this is like no space at all. It's like this much space
They literally like this much and he was like under the couch
He like clawed the bottom of the couch off in this little hole
Climbed inside of it and like hidden there and I was like he's gone
And then he was like came out when he was gone hungry and so
Come on, Luna, jump up, Luna, be a little acrobat.
side of this like busy highway and so I was like
Don't let me see here because I will fall in love with her. I haven't I have too many cats
I cannot have another cat. He's like, well, let me go for 10 minutes. I'll be right back
He left a little case next to me, and I was just watching TV, trying not to look at it, and then she was like,
Trying not to look at it, aww.
Trying not to, and I was looking, and then I was like, and then I opened it, and then she came out, and her eyes were just covered in boogers and stuff.
I got the fleek comb, and I like combed her eyes off, and she opened her eyes, and what did I see, Lolo, when you opened your eyes?
Can you show me your eyes?
Be back in a couple minutes.
Okay, dude.
We can't really see.
I'm gonna stay on panel, I just, uh...
Yeah, turn my
Green I don't know. It's like the lighting is bad, but she has these beautiful green eyes
You can't really see them perfectly, but you know what Lola when I go under the covers
Who's the first one you dart under there you just dart under there and you curl up and you go
And I fall asleep. Okay. Yeah, she's so gorgeous. She's so gorgeous. So lucky. I love I fucking love my cat so much and it's like
In fact, you know that Lady Bathory I know I know she's in chat and she's like nice to people. She's always said
To me animal abuser fraud terrible person
You know, you're sick blah blah blah and and all this stuff and I it's like okay
You're a bitch. How dare you talk to Lady Bathory that way and I was like Lady Bathory has the name of actually this countess
that murdered young like
Teenage girls for and for their blood so she can take a bath in it
And that's your name, but you're calling me a bad per...
I mean, I don't understand it.
Like, call yourself...
Well, Psyche, it would go a long way with her
if you would get the cat fixed.
I know that.
Yeah, but she's, but you know, usually she says,
okay, she's like, I offered, she never offered.
I never, if she would have said,
hey, I'll have my friend come over
and help picture cat, I would have remembered that.
And I would have said, sure.
I mean, I'll take any help I can get.
But she's like, she just says she said it.
And it's like, and it's like just so annoying
because she's lying.
and it's like and then it's like I don't know like no one like believes me or listens to me like
about a lot of things but you know I swear to god I swear on my cat's life I swear on my own life
she never offered that to me or she did I never saw it and then or responded or acknowledged
I never I just never saw it if I would have seen that I would have said please please I'd love
Oh, here he is.
He's like, there's tricks.
He's like a daddy's boy.
He stays in the house 90% of the time.
And I also go to the side and he stays like 10 feet away.
And I know, I know.
And yeah, he's one cat I don't have fixed.
And as soon as I can, I will go do it and stuff.
It is not that easy to go Uber to like downtown LA
or like,
Even like half hour away and stuff and then everything. I mean, I I
Gotta get my shit together. I know but I fucking finally clean my house yesterday. I finally fucking
Like, you know got in a nice white shirt and put my hair back and like was like finally like presentable yesterday
but guys I also like
Have been through like some shit, and you know, I've had I've had a like really tough couple like last years
You know, and I know ever and everyone will because everyone will have a
Probably a parent passed away, and it's horrible
And it's like I'm lucky because I had both my parents and then I had you know
My dad lived here like he was 86 years old and so now I have like Christine
like talking about my dead father, talking to like a fake sister.
Actually, my sister's name, my last name, or her last name too,
and her picture saying, oh, I hate my brother.
He's such an annoying person.
And then Christine types in her chat,
oh, I know brother's gonna be so difficult.
And she knows my last name.
Yeah. And so I don't, I don't know. And then she's like, well, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Yes, you do know, Christine. And that's cruel. I mean, it's like really cruel because I never talked about her kids.
The only time I mentioned your son was when she said, told me to jump off a bridge and she means it.
Then she's like, well, don't you know, my son went bridge jumping and it's a sport here in Florida.
And I was like, well, are there crocodiles in the lake? And she's like, yes, it's Florida.
Well shit, everybody knows what she meant when she told you to jump off a bridge.
And she says she means it. She said at least like 10, 15 times and she feels so continue to say it.
And then it's like, but then I'm saying horrible thing. I said Christine, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
But, and they're all mad, and Christine's mad, but Christine's not even her real name.
She named herself after a murdering car from a Stephen King book.
And she's been holding this over my head making me feel guilty for months, so I remembered
she's just full of shit.
Like really full of shit.
I mean, it's like really.
And you know why I said this?
It's because I was hurt and it's like when Ruby was a joke and I don't know.
Entertaining these people in our chat and stuff is just like fucking maddening. It's maddening
It's just a different standard for me, but it's you know what? Hey, I didn't ask for like
Okay, maybe I was like, oh, I want to be an IPQ Benny told me last night
He's like well
I was telling you you didn't want to be on that because there's a bunch of people from the dark web that are like sickos and are
Actually trying to make the streamers commit suicide. Have you heard of the cappers on the cappers Kate?
Okay, look up this thing called the cappers on YouTube and there's this video about
They're like these like people from the Netherlands and like Europe and some in America and they go in chat rooms and they get like underage people to like flash and they get the picture of it and then they start blackmailing them and harassing them and stuff.
And this one girl unalived herself because she couldn't take it anymore.
But then they had an award show about.
Oh, this is the cap of the year.
It's like so sick.
And it's like the fucking it's horrible.
It's really horrible.
What up?
You don't wanna say quack to me?
I have a good day and thank you and I just want to say thank you especially sponsor the uber ride
She's sponsored the tattoo. What the fuck? I can't hear you now. You can't hear me now. I'll leave and come back
Oh, excuse me. Oh
Where'd he go? I just did you hear me now? You hear me? Here you go. Okay. Do you hear less? Let's talk
Well, that's gone. That's gone. Q do you hear me?
Q went somewhere, so he's in the middle. He's in the middle. Hey, you know what Q, stuck in the middle with us.
Okay, here we go. Here's Les is back too.
Is that you Les in the picture? Yeah, that's me. Yeah, that's you. Can you hear me Les? Yeah, I hear you good.
Okay. Oh my god. That's scary.
Why is scary
Cartoon character, it's a cartoon character. I just made it out
Can you make it? Can you are you gonna make a cartoon of me as a duck?
No, I don't mean to power the duck. Yes. No, it's easy do those. I don't do those. You see today, okay?
Okay, easy. Well, I'm gonna I don't do I don't do ducks
You don't do you're not in the duck. You're on the crackers
You were asking about um the picture of the lady that started with an a yeah, I have that picture in video
And my phone did die. I can't believe I got home
My shit and I told her about my shit is public
I don't care about my my address and all that shit because I already said my
Here can I show
I'll show you have you seen her picture yet. Mm-hmm. I always saw what somebody showed me bow
I wasn't sure it was the same picture. No
All right, hold on
You can do it is your profile. I'm some Kate or do you want me to bring something up? Oh
It's up to you I we can do either here either way either way whatever is easier for you
Who's that is that dumb dead Louise
Here and if you if you want proof that it's really her
Hold on. Let me make sure
Oh wait, I don't know. We use from it. You're on camera
Yo, I mean something over all the pictures show me by what's it's good
Yeah, you're talking about Amanda, right?
We're not gonna identify her. Can I be doxxing her name starts with an A and her last name starts with an E
Lace first you're eating. Wow. It's crazy. Yo, that's fucking crazy. And if you want to hear the voice
What's the voice? The voice with it hold on I can prove that it's her
Here I shared it
All right
I heard it
Alexa say Alexa I
Don't want to like get like military involved. We'll call our big Mandy. We know it's our holy shit
Hey
Guys, this is the one I did of this like you know, there's a chicken that keeps
That's crazy
You guys you guys heard of bronze chicken
He's creepy looking is he got dead? I wonder if the picture really if he's got dead eyes
Well, I have the original photo. I had it like slightly
Altered a little bit so it was more AI and stuff, but I can show you the real original picture too
I mean that I got you're not forgot. Yo, I forgot you I had you ass on
My own on YouTube I forgot
Yes. Look at his teeth.
People will say, oh, that's not real.
I have the actual video it came from, too,
and he's talking about his being gangstocked
on the county bus and stuff.
Time, do you have a problem with it, Time?
Well, he also was a model in his early days.
This is modeling days.
Time, do you have a problem with it?
I showed it. I showed it. Time. Do you have a problem? Time. Time just said her name. Time. No one said her. No one said any name. You just said her name. So, time. Alexa, be mad at that person. Time actually said her name. But I have the case. I did. I'll take blame for it. Time. Not psyche. I showed it.
Nah, I'm going yo. I know I know I know why she loves yo
Obviously, yo, what I do about better is every ride. I've literally been Kate and Kate has been on cam
I've been I've been on cam for like thousands of hours like you can literally find every single fucking
Purple angle and every time I'm figuring those were dirty and stuff like that. Oh, yo Kate. You still you still beat you still beat the what Christine?
Hell yeah
Yo
On my page right you go to my short clip
Will you go if you go to my short clip you you will see you will see your own
Song I mean it's a picture and it's a song and I got the youtuber. She's in the hospital down with you to shit
Here
Watch this one guys watch this video real quick
What's your page left?
I know this has happened before. Every time I make a comment on a page,
like somebody will follow up behind me and like...
What's that?
Startin' trouble or something?
I feel people, so then they, you know...
And then, like, they think it was me, but...
Imagine that guy sitting next to you in the bus,
and you're just gonna be like, all over the place.
She's having a suit on me, like, suit on me.
He's definitely on drugs.
He can't have the exact same thing, so he'll put it in, like, a copy of that, or some change of that.
I don't think that more improvement is the voice of the buses.
Right, I'll read that. Awesome.
Okay, Kate, Kate, how much does it cost to spell that mask? How much, how much?
I wouldn't do it for, like, a thousand dollars.
Yo, Kate, it's low at East Side Podcast TV.
Okay. Okay. L is lower east side.
I can put your less. Are you a
mod? You should be a mod here
because the whole quackers
thing is a mod now. Yeah, I
don't got it. You never gave me
one. Okay. I think it's bad.
I'm in the chat right now. I'll
give you. I don't know if I'm
blocked or not. You're not
blocked. If you are, I'll go.
I'm blocked you. I'm lost you.
I got you. I got you right now.
Say, okay. Step in the chat.
I'll mod you. I got you.
and where is it I'll get the link for you the short video okay you type in the
chat less type in the chat got you okay okay got you
We're all good. There you go. Yeah, but now you can post links in the chat. You go to the shorts, you see it.
I can't type on the chat because I'm on a different advice. Okay, I got you, but can I salute your shorts?
Yeah, I'll care. Okay. You're actual, I'm talking about your boxer shorts.
Never mind, never mind, never mind.
Wasn't that a Nickelodeon video?
Yes.
Remember the guy from Different Shokes?
He was the redhead from Different Shokes?
He was in that show, Slayer Shores?
And he turned into like this like scarier looking guy.
But when he was on different strokes,
he was a kid that got, he got kidnapped.
And then Mr.
And then he got kidnapped by this family and stuff.
And then they rescued him.
And he's like, Mr. D.
And he ran towards when they rescued him.
And he's like, Sam, his name was Sam, I think.
Do you remember, remember, remember that?
I'm getting chills.
That's it.
I have eighties chills whenever I talk about the eighties.
I'm sorry.
Christine and Summer have a GB database of pictures
they looked up.
Oh, you know what's funny is like I was asking the whole thing on Amanda
I was saying Amanda Christine and sweet people were like saying oh, we're gonna get the body cam footage from your
My my arrest or like when the police came to my door and so I asked Amanda
I was like, do you know anything about these body cam?
I never heard of a body cam footage and then RG came on and said Amanda
You're bullshitting because you know you talk all about the body cam footage
We know all about the body cam footage and you talk about it all the time
What, RG?
I mean, it's like, Jesus.
I mean, please.
Sorry.
I loved her and RG against each other.
That was hilarious.
That was funny.
That wasn't that crazy, guys?
Do you remember that episode of Different Shokes?
Hey, you know what I have?
Okay, so I have a cousin.
He's like my grandma's brother's grandson
or something like that.
So he was like some kind of cousin or something.
His name is Bill.
And he was gay and like my mom loves him because it's like, you know, she had a gay cousin and, you know, she had a, you know, lesbian sister gay cousin, but we went to lunch and stuff.
And he was so nice and he, but he was like the showrunner for different strokes, the facts of life and good times for those shows.
They gotta electrocute it in the pool and dive.
Yo, yo, Psyche. Yo, Psyche, you need to get a logo like this.
Let me see your logo. What is that?
Right here. Right here. I'm emoji.
You're emoji? Yeah. I need to get that.
Yeah, yeah, you get like that.
Well, I look mean and stuff. I can make one in 10 seconds.
Okay. Let me, I'll be right back. Okay.
All right, but I'm going to make it intense.
I like how Psyche do his own graphic.
That's his fishy.
Well, seniors, whack.
How much does smell KZ's face mask?
Neggs, you're disgusting.
Oh, shit.
You nasty.
What else is there?
Are you guys good?
It was just a question.
Whoa
Hi, nor grace hi charisma
Yo, I was first that picture got me laughing
Know right
I got it. I got it. I got it.
That's a joke. That's a joke.
That was that was that was
Look at me. Guys, look at me
now. Look at me now. Look at
me now. Oh, that's a
Okay, you have to do the one with the movie the one with the movie with it
You're holding your whole your whole arm psyche come up like the psyche may come up with the movie the little logo like this with the movie
I'm gonna say good psyche or something like that. I don't know. I don't know good
What is that from like a Warner's brother theme yeah
Yeah
My my my homeboy crack he made he made one of those and then I just took one of his and that's it
I told him make my make minds just like that and I just put my name and this came up like that
And then I just put my little character
My little cartoon character. You know me
This is as far as I got with my AI skills. I got my little that's just hot. That's just hot
That's just the issue
Make a cartoon Amanda. Oh shut up
Stop can you get you put it backstage or or something or oh?
No, I can get it again, because I'll make I can do something. Well, here's what it did
Here's what I have now. This is my my second one. I did. Let me see. I'll put my here we go. Okay
How about this one? Is this okay? I said add a logo home and how does this look at less and Kate and
Q once again, how does this one look?
I
Was official see psyche
There you go mobster psyche. Hey, I'm born Al Capone's birthday. Oh really?
Yeah. Well, you know what?
So, I'll, so, AM, I won't say her name.
You know what the name is.
But she was like, well,
Psyche and I were born on the same birthday,
but she's like, actually, if you go like by the,
the trajectory of the sun,
she's like, I'm actually,
I should be born January 8th.
And she's like, so I'm Elvis.
And she goes, thank you very much.
Oh, since my baby left me,
and she starts singing Elvis.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
Okay, I'm on the cusp. I know that
Okay, okay got it for you. Okay, okay eight two three
Well 23 is a really cool number. Okay, so okay, I got this for you
Okay, it's called
Okay, this is a video. I gotta get the actual website. Sorry, one sec. Yeah
Okay
Okay, I think I got it, okay
Okay, and then I didn't see the change the birthday
But wasn't that fun guys did we have some fun here in the meantime, I'm gonna play the Chris K video
You can see Chris K get beat up
I think he got beat up by manual Lewis or might have been Gary Coleman. There's
There is some like controversy there cusps are intense because you got the best of both worlds in them, but this is the
This is Chris K getting punched by Emanuel Lewis or Gary Coleman. I'm not a hundred percent sure
Which one it was you guys would help me identify it I would love that I think it's as fast as
There you are.
On average, they're saving their customers.
You understand?
Hey, don't get the suit off your pool, partner.
You better check yourself.
What do you do about it?
I ain't no pussy.
Now, get on camera, do all that.
I ain't no front row.
You better check yourself.
I don't give a fuck who you got with you.
Check yourself, partner.
Shit.
Hey.
You can't fussy.
What the fuck?
Snap it.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to go to jail.
Winner of one is on the back.
Yeah, what's up?
What's up?
Fuck this nigger.
No?
Don't let him watch you talk.
What's up?
What's happening?
I bet
Now what?
Yeah
You don't want NOBODY
Back that!
Look at that, look at that
Get it on there
Get that on there
Bet you don't want nobody I bring around here
Now what?
Exactly
You gotta fuck
You ready to check?
Holy shit, fuck you!
Fuckin' about, bro!
What are you talkin' about?
Come on, man!
You wanna get your ass over there?
Get your ass over there!
I got it. I got it. I found it. Okay, so hold on. Yeah, I got something for you. Okay, let's see.
Oh, no.
Oh, my god.
Is that? I feel like I'm in Alice in Wonderland.
Wow.
See you guys, guys, you have to rewind the screenshot that ends up, okay?
That's a good one. I'm gonna do five, four, three, two. Yeah, that is good.
Wait now you made that I did
That was fucking good Kate
Okay, I have your I have your birthday your your birthday is called a day of lively precision is an intense
Poise technical self-involve that's a positive self-involved detached and a mad emotionally blocked
Okay, and it says
Let me see. Okay. So your birthday. So the report for this is
Got it. Okay. So it says here's some advice for you
Try to stay sensitive to the feelings of others
But more importantly get in touch with your own needs on a deeper level
Keep aggressive urges under control while remaining uninhibited give con a conscious effort to give
unconditionally and don't lose yourself and a material concern and
Like I meant I want to find like the actual that does have like a
Okay one second
Eight times 23. Okay. I'll get out of the book. I have them. I can get the book real quick
I'm sorry, but that's so far that's pretty good. I can read you that I can actually get the August 23rd, okay
Got it, okay
Um, okay
And I've downloaded it here I can read it here. Okay, perfect. Okay
Okay, oh my gosh, I wish I had the book I gave the book to my neighbors because that we went out
I got drunk and like I read it to them one night, but it should be on
Yeah, it should be on this website though. I don't know why it's like not
Excuse me. Okay. Okay. Actually sln.me is the website. It's like an app. Okay. And I can okay. I can change it. Okay
And I can change it to august 23rd
Okay, come on
Because today's april 3rd, right? Okay. Okay. Look up a birthday. Got it. Got it. Okay august
23rd, okay
report. Okay, summary. Okay. So I said lively precision. So they have lively precision.
And report. Here we go. Okay. This website's all messed up. All messed up. Okay, I'll read
Under health it's a okay, so it says
Okay
Okay, it says, help.
Those born on August 23rd are prone
to various psychological difficulties,
the most common being emotional inhibition.
Too often their feelings are conveyed in an abrupt manner
or in extreme cases they can withdraw into a shell
and become numb to pain.
Psychological counseling is strongly recommended
for August 23rd people suffering from such difficulties.
As far as diet is concerned,
August 23rd people may not be able to handle excess sugar,
although they often crave it.
and this sensitivity along with potential food allergies should be kept in mind.
As mentioned above, vigorous and regular physical exercise is highly recommended for
the intense people born on this day. And competitive sports such as competition not
only provides a chance to experience a thrill of victory but an opportunity to demonstrate
So those born in the 23rd are ruled by the numbers 2, 2, 3, which equals 5, and by the planet Mercury.
Mercury represents quickness of thought and change, qualities heightened by August 23rd people, as Virgo is ruled by the planet.
Sun influences from the Leo side of the cusp, here may indicate aggressiveness.
Whatever hard knocks or pitfalls those ruled by the number 5 encounter in life, they usually recover quickly.
Um, and for August 23 people, this enhances the above mentioned quest for exciting people
and experiences.
And then your, um, your card is the Hierophant, an interpreter of sacred mysteries who is symbolic
of human understanding and faith.
His knowledge is esoteric and he has authority over things unseen.
Favorable traits conferred by this card are self-assuredness and insight.
emphasizing the need for august 23rd people to be more aware of the concerns and thoughts of others
and uh and then yeah so it said and here's a here's a meditation it says the greatest achievement
of a truly ambitious person may be simple kindness and then it says famous people born on this day
Scott Khan, Ray Park, Jay Moore is born in your day.
Rick Springfield, Shelley Long.
Oh, Shelley Long is cool.
Barbara Eden, I dream of Jeannie.
Yeah, let me see if I can get any more.
Okay, it says, okay, so it says day.
Okay, so it's just famous people.
Week.
Okay, it says don't, it says here's advice.
Oh, that the weak is that's the weak.
Oh, let me go Pat.
Your path is called revelational exposure.
Learning to trust the intuitive is understanding of others.
Your fulfillment will be putting your unique talents on public display.
It says, although this was born in the cup of exposure,
who traveled the way of revelation may not be entirely.
may not never entirely be able to gain from others
the same level of understanding the offer to the world,
these remarkable personalities should take care
to respect their own special brand of insight
and resist the impulse to second guess their best hunches
or turn on themselves when they encounter rejection
or disapproval.
Though they may be self-conscious in the extreme,
these individuals have a tremendous need
to gain acceptance and approval
through well-timed self-revelation.
If properly acknowledged and not discounted as mere neediness, this quality will help
them rise above the narrow restrictions of self and into the world of spirit.
The ability to put themselves, their ideas, and their talents on view in areas such as
teaching, the performing arts, or other public pursuits will best be able to combine and
employ their special gifts in a way that benefits all.
And so I hope you enjoyed that. I mean, I will if you want to if you want me to do your your chart and stuff like that
You can just like, you know, you can contact me and I'll I'll run your chart
I can also like give you like tons of information, you know, of course because you're my friend, you know
I'm happy to do that for you. So awesome. That was insightful
Cool. Yeah, I'm I was born on the day of unusual interests, you know
Um, oh, and I love this, but look at the how artistic is case like, oh
Look she did a perfect
She really did
The everyone I swear the AI will take your like natural like
Whatever like some we all have natural
Strengths and it can take it and it's like and she just has this idea take this picture and
Do this with it, and I love the Alice in Wonderland
The caterpillar. I mean, it's great. That's just really really really good. I'm impressed
Thanks. Yeah, and like I couldn't have done it without my my inspiration
Shout out to you ma'am
know she's lost weight I'm sure she has well you know what it's time to put
time to time for her to put her a new foot because she was like oh I'm waiting
to see my new photo the Pokemon Tarot is even more I forgot all about the time
what home reading times comment oh my god oh my gosh I just lost them I'm so
sorry I forgot all about the Pokemon Tarot
I want the Pokemon tear. I mean, I can read the Pokemon tear. I'm really
I want to do a quick reading for you. Okay. That was funny
Those ones poking fun at psyche. Sorry about that. It's okay. It's okay. I mean, I just timed him out for a few minutes
Okay, Kate. You got the devil. Okay. This is the first card you got. Oh
Those are pretty cards because this devil doesn't really have like because usually there's slaves and stuff in the devil car
But this is just I think this is just
Um
You being like really in touch with your earthly self and like able to like
Kind of be a ruler on the earth a master of the earth, okay?
I think like you have this control like self-control
You have this like ability to control people. Okay king of wands
This could be a man in your life or something like that, but this is like and there's a castle right there
I don't really is there the king there. I mean
I don't know it looks like but it looks like just like some kind of like
inspiration that can lead to some big great stability and I see kind of the
towers I'm almost thinking of Rapunzel like you're gonna let somebody up with
your hair like you know just use a weave so it doesn't pull too hard on your
scalp
Time I okay. It was a joke time. It was a joke. It was a joke. You're fine. Also two of cups
There's some romance. There's about actually either romance or a great partnership coming for you
Okay, like a really good like you each have like something the other one that just complements each other
I think I get a joke time
But I'm those are beautiful cards. Thank you. Yeah, yeah, I got you know some of these cards
I got on T moon sup and but yeah, I think these pink ones are really beautiful
We also have the six of six of swords
Okay, so this six of swords look at this. It's like it so this is like, you know, you can this is a victory definitely
You know and six is a lover's car also and this is like almost like with that two of cups
I think there's gonna be a victory in love even wanting and I was also oh, yeah
So, uh, also, but it could be
like, kind of like, because
this reminds me of kind of a
merry-go-round a little bit.
It could be going round and
round and round.
Right?
But I think you'll eventually
get victory in this because
doesn't that kind of remind you
of the merry-go-round with the
big, big, uh, the thing?
Oh, the, um, the carousel.
Yes.
Carousel.
Right.
It's like with the, the horse
and stuff.
But the horse is like, it's
still, it's like, it's like a
ride and stuff like that.
Oh.
It's like a blind spot, but it's like you have to use your intuition by something also you got you cut off a couple guys heads. Oh
Yeah, and but and see and it's like maybe these heads you cut off it could be your eyes
You can you can be holding these and they can kind of be your eyes for this and you can like close your eyes
You know, I don't think it's gonna be a blind spot, but it's also like
It's usually these two swords and you know what two swords are like a scissors
Okay, okay time calm down time. I mean just a few more three more
Well, this is this is wealth coming this is like the Tana pinnacles
Oh, and it's like as above so below
Okay, but it's also like that that star it's like you know and people say this is good this evil
But it's like we're both right we remember like sometimes the the shadow side is more just like this a reflection
It's a shadow of like the real
The real us and it's like but we need the shadow be like we need it
It's like or else we wouldn't have reflection imagine looking your mirror and y'all reflect. It's a vampire energy, right?
So you have the energy
also
Like I said, okay, so this particular one it's like even in an even in like difficult times like you have support and
Love and it's like and like you can support each other
Maybe if you're like left out of something, but it's like also in this one like there's somebody at the door
Maybe they're saying no, no, you can't come in here. No, no, no, you're not welcome or whatever and that's like that's it
but it's like
Hey, there's it's called two against one, you know, you like, you know, like let go the you know
You're going go go go go fucking pick that guy's pocket or bite him or something. Okay?
You also got the wheel of fortune. So so luck is gonna be in your favor. Okay. Good time to like maybe buy a
Scratcher, I always think that but it's also like I think the I think of this particular one is like you
Have done good and it's like the good will be returned to you and it's like you're in a very
a good, lucky, prosperous time.
I'm gonna do one more card.
Awesome.
And the final card, seven of wands.
This is like you're protected.
This feel protected?
It's like, you don't, you haven't let yourself
be hurt to the point of like,
You're so traumatized. You can't let anybody in you're you're you're you're open to let people in but it has to be the right person
It has to be like
There's a face right there to you almost like a face there. So there's like something
It's it's like something watching over and it's kind of a little bit of scary face there, but I think it's like
Why is in a way and there's a wheel again? There's a wheel again and remember the wheel will always go around and round
You know you have your ups and downs and things like that
but you're basically in the upright and
I'll look at almost like the two hands there too. It looks like two hands. What is that look right?
Looks like running like Bram Stoker
Remember the Bram Stoker is Dracula and the guy in Bram Stoker is Dracula like this world
This world kind of takes from us and we give and the world takes sometimes
But remember I just think past that you have this like
Protection up again, so no one's gonna know like no one that you don't want it
I think there's a door you can open for them if they want to come in but no one's gonna get in without
You letting them in and so and also I see I see I
like
Sometimes I get like a mask that you know how masks can be scary and stuff and people will be scared
but it's a mask and it's like
It's just a mask and that kind of really reminds me of a mask and it's like I think that
You want to you want to show the people your real self, but only the people that deserve it like the people like you will
Maybe have a rough exterior, but if people get to know you
You'll you'll you'll take off the mask and there's like a smiling face and like a like a laugh and like a kind person behind there
And it's like so that's pretty accurate
So that's my everything. I hope you like that. Awesome
Thank you so much psyche. I love you. I mean, I love you like seriously
When we started out together, we were like you're like, I don't know about this guy
I was like, I don't know about her. We did he had mistrust
You know, I was like on this one, you know beat a train or whatever like insane and stuff
And and all this stuff, but you always treated me well
You always did and that's even when I was like, oh this bitch
I'm gonna go over there and give her a piece of my mind and you're like
Like hey come on up come on up my panel and let's have a chat and you let me say whatever I wanted to say
You never interrupt me say. Oh, you're my your piece of shit. You I hate you
You're doing this in this wrong. You're always gracious and I'll say he's a great person
Take a copy and Kate. She's and also I know a good heart when I see like I really oh, oh my who's this?
I'll borrow. I like you guys. You're not 300 glow though, are you? I'm not Mexican. Are you Guatemalan? Ecuadorian?
Which one? You're one of the three. Keep on talking. El Salvadorian. El Salvadorian. Yeah,
but keep on talking. Yeah, El Salvadorian. I love El Salvadorians. I love Mermaid and I love Beta.
I love you. Thank you. I love you, too. What about me a baron? I love Kate
I love getting tattoos. I don't even like getting tattoos. I don't know what you're doing. That one. That's a ugly tattoo
You know, I don't even like it
Let me peel it off a little bit. Yeah, put it off
It's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly because it's ugly
That's you got that on you bro. Get the fuck out of here
Your body for ever for some internet shit
My body that BKG on my body forever when I'm in the I'm in the
I got tattoos too, bro. You ain't the only one I got
My fucking
I want to see your leg
Fucking eagle
I want to see it.
I don't know how.
Can I like an ego?
Yeah.
The point is I would never get a tattoo with so many bras.
I like it though.
It looks nice.
Look at he said it sucks, and then I feel the back a little bit. He's like
I look bad when it was beyond the the gauze and stuff like that, but it looks good under I promise you I like getting tattoos
Just for one reason bro
Cuz I like I like how it feels. It feels good. Really like the pain. Hey, how about it?
Tell me you don't like it. It feels good
Hey, you know what, the entire time I got attached to you,
I felt like it was like zero.
Pain
It was like a little bit like if I felt it feels like you know, you're taking a ballpoint pen and like going kind of like
I'm not gonna talk about it. I'm not I'm not here to talk about shannon
The one leg you motherfucker
I don't know anything. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't know anything. I don't
What?
I didn't like it.
What do you think hurts more?
My foot hurts worse.
What?
Losing a leg or getting a tattoo.
I'm sure losing a leg hurts worse.
So what the fuck are we complaining about?
Now I will say the one on my side. I didn't hurt at all hurt like compared to like my foot
That's by the yeah, okay
No, I don't have I have my leg is kind of covered up one of my legs my right leg that should hurt
I didn't hurt at the beginning hurt at the end. I was like man, bro
How long is it gonna take bro? I started farting bro like I was like what the fuck wonder the fuck this shit? Oh my god
That's what happened to me. So I had on my the top of my foot done and they had me like laying down
Right my knees bit
And so she's like right there and oh my god, I defart so bad. I was like
Fucking he just started coming on
That I'm a whole like it's that I don't even know is that this they heard that shit fucking heard at the end bro
It didn't hurt. No, I don't want to say it hurt because it wasn't like pain. I was just like man
It's just irritating at this point. I know it right. I
Don't think that's who's hurt is to get irritating as long as they go
I got my fingers tatted and all that shit. That shit don't hurt. Oh, I guess the figures don't hurt
It just get all my tattoos. I've got to know when I'm drunk, too, but
That don't hurt to just feel irritating if you do it long enough
Right
I'm sorry
That's a good one taking it one. Okay. I had an idea. I was like I just out safe huff marshal
I'm gonna tell you I'm gonna ask you a question, bro
And I'm not I'm indifferent. I don't pick tight
But I heard beat up talking about you talking about her and we're streaming her and I'm gonna be know what's going on here
I'm not allowed to be streamer. She's a leisure. Oh, I agree. We stream it should be allowed by everybody
Hey, she talks about me for hours and hours.
I can't restrain her like for five minutes with Saman.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't like it.
Shit, I'm all for it.
But yeah, well, I guess,
I guess I agree with you why she complained.
I apologize.
I don't know.
I have no idea.
I, I'm about to strike you.
And then I was like, okay, I'll just fucking end it.
I don't even, go, don't fill the five minute form
or whatever.
Did it hurt?
We didn't the tattoo didn't hurt it felt like and the guy was really cute too
And the guy let me like like everyone there is super nice like really super nice. Yeah, that dude was nice
He was cool. Oh
Yeah, I was I was I was fucking drunk and like dumb and like
The chat was saying like in Q and he was saying stupid shit
The guy is sitting there just like it's smiling and then and then I like I didn't have money
And I was like and then I had to leave I came back and they all looked shocked that I came back. They're like
We knew like you came back and there's like no one thought I would
Because I've been on the street like there's like nobody seems to take credit cards or something like that
And so I've had a haircut several times
The people are like, I'll be right back. I'll be right back. I'll go get the ATM
And the per people never come back and it's like that's fucked up. I mean, it's like it's crazy
It's not like I mean if you can't afford a haircut just cut your hair yourself. I mean it
Oh, I don't like I don't have a haircut and I don't because I don't like one, but hey Kate
Do you know what's picture I'm using?
That these that who is that yes, okay?
Yes, would you agree that like nothing in her eyes were fucking uncrosser eyes?
That might do the trick. Hey,
gotta nut them to make them
bitches. That might do the
trick. That might be it. It
might give her pink eye but
Oh wait, that's poop that causes pink eye.
I guess it was a, oh, spunky.
I was like, I was like, look at me,
you're perfect for me.
How do my eye look?
She's like, you have pink eye.
I really don't, but you can see my eye color a little bit.
It's a haze.
It's not brown.
Where is Spunky? She didn't even get a tattoo.
Is she here today? I know. She wasn't even here.
You're right. You're right.
Guys, guys. Guys, I just want to say too, she didn't only pay for the tattoo, she paid for the Uber.
Like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, she's like, really cool.
Who pays for tattoos?
Well, I want to get I want to get my whole chest
Okay, so our first of all go to start a show go on camera get a tattoo with be his initials and then a year later
Like then then ask somebody, okay?
I mean everyone would like that, but it's like really I needed I needed this and it's like
Like she is so awesome. Thank you so much. How much I gotta pay for you to get your forehead tatted
Can I can I haven't tatted it with the picture of your dick? Yeah, you can have a tatted with a picture of my dick
Well, where do you live Venice, I live in Hollywood, bro
They get the outline tatted on your fucking forehead
Okay, I'm not gonna. Oh, I'll get it on my hairline. I'll get it like
That's good enough for you
And it's that big and they're gonna reach all the way that big. Okay. What are you one inch?
You're not you're a smaller than I'm probably not one inch, but not definitely not four inches. Oh
my god
Who would admit that Kate?
me
He ain't a fucking liar ain't gotta be a liar, bro
But do you have the anteater thing or are you circumcised?
I got the anteater thing.
Oh my god. Can you imagine a four inch under that?
I'll fucking shit on your head while they're fucking doing that.
What the fuck is the problem?
I don't want it. I don't want it to get it. Never mind.
You don't want it? You don't want it?
Give me $10,000. Maybe I'll consider it.
Is that okay?
I don't know if that would matter for you.
Okay. Oh my god.
Okay, give me a give me a rice and bean dinner with a enchilada
Hey
$500 a year
I'm not Mexican
El Salvadorian, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Well, I was born in the U.S., bro, but that doesn't matter.
Well, no, I remember you saying you didn't like Mexicans very much.
You said Mexicans are kind of like...
I don't like Mexicans or blacks. What's your point?
Well, I like them in my mouth.
You like them in your mouth?
Yeah. But you know what my favorite thing is? El Salvadorians, because they're spicy.
I'm so sorry am I talking am I
am I on the air guy I'm off the
we're off we're talking privately
right oh my god why is there only
23 people here I'll bear a spicy
I'll bear a spicy
Either leg. I wish I could chop off her other leg. Amen to that
that fuck
But that would be then didn't she wouldn't have to hop around on one leg
Let's hop off her other leg and beat her to death with that fucking leg. Oh my god. Okay guys guys
I mean, I don't like this woman, but I mean it's like come on. I mean, oh that bitch is a fucking horrible human being
Even so
It's like I don't want to be I don't want to be a chicken nugget with a hell of a chicken
gonna be a chicken nugget she's gonna be a fucking chicken dead
chicken bone
well chicken dead
a pollo morce that's what you mean
I love a pollo loco by the way
That's crazy chicken
No, I don't know yeah, but for your locals good man. That shit is delicious
I've gone all over the US I never seen that shit another states that are like in the
East coast or the middle of the country I never seen point local. What's it? You said shut up recharge to me
Absolutely, but that's not the point you show you're on right now
No mine
All right shut up retard I never seen Paul local anywhere else besides
Damn
That's a band a retard
Twice even after he knew you should have known better
Hey, I saw the host you like mermaid cake
I love Mermaid. Hi, Mermaid.
Yeah, Maria's talk shop. Hey, we have a place called, what's the place called? It's called El Tarasco.
And they used to call it El Trash, like the trash can in high school and stuff, but everyone would go there and stuff.
And one time there were these two blonde girls in my class, and they both showed up at the same time.
And they had like a fucking Desperate Housewives water fight with the you know
They just like threw something to the space at the elder. It was a legendary day
Hello moto my tip my phone's talking to me
It had a motor
Don't call me motor the Sandman calls me in private stop it
Oh my god
Must be a California thing like in and out in and out as a fucking bomb place to it. That's good
Never been there. Hey my Russian friend said she might stop by tonight, but she's working right now
I think she has a job at in and out and
That's a fucking good place like it's a good place to work to you know in California. You know what minimum wage is in California?
but
It's like 23 or $25 no shit. Yeah
That's like way more than I am if I was if I was to work at McDonald's I would be like you you fucking see me
I mean I'd have a first of all I buy a car
so second
It would start dressing in like suits and ties
I mean, it's like I would make how much money would that be a day if I worked a six-hour shift?
$150 a day
Okay, three hundred six and nine thousand at least make four thousand dollars a month
Well, yeah, like
How much is it?
23 different $25 an hour
Even 23 if you worked part-time say
For our room over four hours a hundred dollars a seven thousand dollars or seven hundred dollars a week
That's three thousand dollars a month. That's thirty six thousand dollars a year
I mean, it's like not like great, but it's like
Am I making $36,000 a year now for like handing people a pre-made like fucking McDonald's?
Yeah, but how much is rent?
Well, I bet how cost of living is probably
Rent's expensive, but there's benefits to
Coming from real estate tycoons, right? Well for you. Yeah, see minute you want to know how much the minimum wage in Iowa is
Seven dollars and twenty five cents an hour. Wow
Look, yeah, for me. Is it California? Like that would be like
$20 an hour for most people would be like you're homeless. I mean, it's like basically it can't afford right
Yeah, it's like it's like still kind of low in California
If I was to live in like a southern state, I would be in a mansion right like my I would just be them
I would be like fucking if we see midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil
No, okay. I really recommend that was a book on midnight in the garden of good good and evil and it's about
This guy he goes to investigate this town called Savannah, Georgia. Have you heard of that town? Mm-hmm
It's a man of Georgia. It's a beautiful, beautiful city, right?
And, um, really gothic and kind of stuff.
And so this, and so the guy goes to investigate this murder.
And the guy, I guess, is Kevin, um, Kevin Spacey is the guy that plays the millionaire and stuff.
And he, like...
You know, you'd have these people come in and like sell them drugs and stuff and like one of the guys like shoot some one night, you know
And so the guy comes to investigate and there's like a transgender person of all like a black transgender woman
That looks like AM. I can't say her name, but it's like, you know, she looks like AM
And it's like and it's such a good movie if you can like maybe I'll try to
Okay, I'm doing on YouTube, but on kick or twitch. I'll try to like tell everyone to go over there. We can watch that
Like everyone can watch that because it's such a good movie.
I watch it when I was in high school.
I love movies and stuff.
And it's all about Savannah and Savannah is a very, and it's like
there's graveyard scenes and it's like that.
It's a really cool graveyard with all this like sculptures in
the graveyards.
You should be Lieutenant Governor Dan Patrick received $700,000
from special donors at the liquor wine and beer.
Wow.
Hey, do you know about my friend Danny stranger?
You remember him?
Mhm.
Did you see the video memorial for him? I did you did. Okay, did anybody ever get arrested for that?
No, I want to I just want to play real quick. It's only a couple minutes, but no one got arrested and Paige was like
Channeling last night and she picked up on him and I'm really gonna go hang out with Paige instead of hanging with me
Because he always liked women and stuff. Do you remember Piranha that person?
uh-huh
Yeah, so
I introduced her to Danny and stuff and then he kicked me out of his chat
And then she got me back in there by saying hey psychies a good guy and he just trusted her word and stuff
But when I she watches my show still she she told me several months ago
I'm not gonna talk to you more than let's get a job so I blocked her
But then she wrote me on what's app recently say oh, hey, thank you. This is you as a hey
Do you know Danny passed away? She was yeah, yeah, I heard about that
And I said, hey, you know what?
He had mentioned, hey, where's Piranha and stuff?
She's really cool.
You know, we should come back here.
And I was like, but you know how he loved the ladies and stuff.
And she wrote back, ew, well, this is a great conversation.
And I blocked her again.
That was the end of that.
But can you believe that?
And then Beat It called him Danny Danger and how lame I
am for being sad about it.
And then today, she said, she got his name right, I think.
Hey, Danny, I remember four days before he passed away.
I sent my chat over to his chat 40 people went to his chat. He had like 45 people
The first time he always had three or four people in his chat. He had 45 people in his chat
He was I was like you just got rated by psyche. He said it's a bad time
He's like it's about time my bro, and he said you know what if you get 100 people in here
I'll give you a kiss on the lips and stuff and anyway didn't get a hundred people in there
So there was never I also wanted to buy it. Well, you'll hear the song. Yeah, I mean if you hear the song
But it's like I'm not this is like
Nothing to offend anybody, nothing to exploit anybody.
I'm not getting paid.
None of my videos are monetized, like none of them.
And his friends like this video and stuff.
If you don't mind, I'm just gonna, it's a quick video.
I'm sure I've seen it.
Yeah, this is him, he's doing these,
he's doing these like a couple shots of like,
he just takes beers, pours them in,
and then he like takes them in a second.
But I didn't get the end of it.
I just got it when he was pouring them and stuff,
but you can see him touching or peeking up his cat and stuff.
It's really, it's really sweet.
Here he is.
This is Rest in Peace, Danny Stranger.
And enjoy guys, and I'll be right back guys.
Is it on the screen? Here we go.
Perfect.
By the way, Kate, I wrote this song,
and I played it for him on his show,
like, several months before,
because one last year, I said,
can I be a mod before I was even on my stream?
And he's like, yeah, and then...
I was like, well, I wanted him to dance in his boxer shorts and stuff.
I think I paid him $35.
He danced in his boxers.
It was one of the best in my life.
And then it's like, and then I was like, then recently I was asking him, can I buy your
wife beater?
You know what he said when I asked him, if I could buy his wife beater?
He said, it's called a, it's called a white beater.
They're not called white.
They're called white.
I said, they're called wife beaters, Danny.
He never knew they were called white beaters.
Oh, damn.
Yeah, crazy.
I'm actin' normal, yeah, sure, okay
But my brain's yellin' open, I'm made your way
He did one little dance, and my soul said,
Fine, now I'm losin' my dignity one beat at a time
I don't hit him up much, I keep it tight
Cause he's got that charm that can wreck my night
One smile on hate, and I'm already sure
He'll talk me into somethin' expensive, love
Danny stranger, you're trouble, you're a kid
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks in a pack
You dance for me once now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual while I'm losing my tracks
And no, he ain't gay so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much cause I know what he'll do
He'll talk me in the bottom of a whole dang truck
And I don't even ever back do
He got that I might be a problem grand Like he's selling sunshine with a citizen
He laughs, I fold my wallet, get scared I'm tryna play cool, but I'm deeply unprepared
I'm not sayin' I'm obsessed Just molly deranged like who needs self-respect
When the vibes is strange I keep my distance, I do my best
But he pops in my head like a bad text
He says we should hang, I'm black maybe soon
Then I hide in my house like a raccoon
Daddy's stranger, your trouble, your cutie tag
I wanna buy your underwear and your socks and a pack
You danced for me once, now I'm down bad facts
But I'm keeping it casual, I'm losing my tracks
And though we ain't gay, so don't make it weird
I'm just out here spiraling crystal clear
I don't talk to him much cause I know what he'll do
You would talk me into buying him a whole dang truck
And I don't even have a bike to
I'm a responsible adult allegedly
But that man says, babe, in my brain
Don't spend money, I'm not his bank
I'm not his plan, I'm just a humble fan
With a morally questionable stance
If he blinks twice, I'm making poor choices
Hearing cash registers like back
voices Danny stranger you're trouble you're a cute attack I wanna buy your underwear and
your socks in a pack you dance for me once now I'm down bad facts but I'm keeping it
casual while I'm losing my track so no he ain't gay so don't make it weird I'm just
out here spiraling crystal clear I don't talk to him that much cause I know what he'll
do he'll talk me in a body mo-
and I don't even have a bite, dude.
Danny Stranger.
Please stop being adorable.
My finances can't take it.
I want to say one thing, like no matter what.
That's a nice tribute.
Thank you.
Now, I mean, I played that song for him a few months ago
and because like he did like,
So I see her to charge me like $5 and I was about to buy him a Ford Ranger at this point
And then I just like stop going to his chat for a while like last year because I can't afford a ranger
But beta I would never if you had a friend that died
I would never keep bringing them up and like mocking you over it. I
Never ever ever said anything about your dead loved ones or anything
And you continually will mock me over Michael and Danny.
And these are my friends before any of you
were friends with them.
I don't understand.
I think it's like cruel.
That's why I think you guys are evil, okay?
Like I would never do that to you.
And so really fuck you.
And that's why fuck BKG.
And I'm so happy with my tattoo.
The tattoo is finally complete.
That's what it was supposed to be the whole time. I just couldn't write the fuck part on top of it last year now
It's finally complete
Fuck you. That's all I was saying
Fuck you for bringing up my dead friends and saying I'm
Exploiting them and stuff like that when it's like they're my life and also I hear them in my ears. I
See here. I hear Michael Michael still comes around Danny still comes around
And you're in a mock me do you mock page when she is channeling them?
Never never, but you're in a mock. Yeah, she won't say anything to page. I bet. Oh, no
And page is dating Benny am I gonna hear oh page, you know, you're getting a child and stuff like that
Are we gonna hear that ever are we gonna hear that we're gonna hear bring your W. Benny
You got this hot hot older chick and stuff. I don't think are they dating?
They're eating now. I think yeah, no, I don't think so. Well, he asked for
She added him and I left him alone and they for having a good time. All it's all a thing dang
Nothing no
What is this?
Wave it in the air like you just don't care. That's your dick
Hey, do I have to end the stream?
It looks like an uncircumcised penis, Kate.
Do I have to end the stream?
That's not a penis.
No.
It's Shannon's nub.
What is that?
Shannon's nub.
Oh, my God.
That was Alvaro's penis.
No, no, no.
It looks like that by the mouth.
Is that what it looks like I'll borrow though it is the kind of look
No, no, no.
Looks like it's long not the long part the skin part the skin part
Get out of here then out
Okay, I don't get these people. I don't get it
What what are they? What are they thinking? Oh
Some fag I can just teeth
I wouldn't if you wanted to grade me me me in person spit in my mouth
Hope me to death and I can die a happy person. But until then stop messing with me. Okay, like you like sit rough rough
I like fuck I like it really rough go putty
You got your Lola
Hold on
He's your Lola. You don't mind if you show her on camera if you want, but you don't have to but I'm taking her out
Hey, she won't go out cuz it's wet
Lenore is interested. Lenore. Hi Lenore, sweet baby girl.
Lenore's a little bit of a lesbian too. Go body!
When my cat Lola had got pregnant and stuff. You go body!
Lenore finally was like
interested in what's going on and the nurse like why can't I get pregnant? I was like Lenore because
You were fixed very early
But like Lola wasn't and Lola got went to the junkyard and got pregnant and had beautiful kid in this stuff
I'll see if I can find it. I don't know if you've seen this. Have you seen the pictures of Lenore when I got her Kate?
Baby Lenore?
I don't know if I've seen the little Lenore
Okay, so you're my Russian friend like my Russian friend actually I had another cat named Salem
Who's a black cat and that ran away and it was a really difficult
Situation because I kept like getting calls. Oh come to this shelter
I think we found her and it was like a different black cat and stuff, but
But and that when I couldn't find her anymore. I
Told them I asked her can you I was like I want a black cat. She brought me a ginger cat that day
His name was Toby and stuff and I love that cat too. He had a car unfortunately, but but that night
There's a knock on the door and she also arranged for like a baby black cat to be to be brought over and that